<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Testbeds on Eclipse IoT</title>
    <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/testbeds/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Testbeds on Eclipse IoT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 10:48:55 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://iot.eclipse.org/testbeds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Asset Tracking</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/testbeds/asset-tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 10:48:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/testbeds/asset-tracking/</guid>
      <description>Leveraging Eclipse Kura for data acquisition and reliable connectivity The Eclipse Kura open source project is used to provide an easy-to-deploy edge computing stack that can run on virtually any IoT gateway device that would typically be found in airport baggage management systems or in a delivery truck.
It is used for communicating with Bluetooth low energy sensors that are attached to valuable parcels that need to be tracked. As Kura provides built-in support for Bluetooth communication, it provides a great starting point for interfacing with the sensors in order to collect data such as temperature, humidity, vibration, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Production Performance Management</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/testbeds/production-performance-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 16:54:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/testbeds/production-performance-management/</guid>
      <description>At the heart of the testbed is the Production Performance Management Protocol (PPMP), which allows uniform representation of all the data and information related to manufacturing processes. The testbed showcases how performance data from different industrial assets can be connected to the same IoT Cloud backend, so that this data can be further processed, or simply visualized.   Standardized communication using PPMP  PPMP specifies a format that allows to capture data that is required to do performance analysis of production facilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Propose a new testbed</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/testbeds/propose-a-new-testbed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/testbeds/propose-a-new-testbed/</guid>
      <description>The Eclipse Open IoT Testbeds are an initiative of the Eclipse IoT Working Group. The testbeds focus on demonstrating how open source, open standards along with commercial solutions can be used to create real-world, industry specific IoT solutions.
If you are interested in proposing a new testbed, you can send an email to iot@eclipse.org. A proposal for a new testbed should include the following details:
 Short description of the scenario High-level architecture Identified extension points List of interested members List of applicable Eclipse IoT projects  In order to lead a testbed, your company needs to be a member of the Eclipse IoT Working Group.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>