<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>White-papers on Eclipse IoT</title>
    <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/white-papers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in White-papers on Eclipse IoT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://iot.eclipse.org/white-papers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Software for Industry 4.0</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/white-papers/industry40/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/white-papers/industry40/</guid>
      <description>Introduction  The Internet of Things (IoT) represents a significant change and opportunity for the manufacturing industry. Technological advancements in connectivity and communication technology, real-time data analysis, and complex event processing have opened the possibility of integrating the traditional operational technology (OT) of a manufacturing plant with the enterprise information technology (IT) systems. This alignment of OT and IT in the manufacturing industry presents a huge opportunity for a more efficient manufacturing process, including tighter integration of the supply chain, preventive maintenance of the factory floor, and more flexibility to react to changing customer demands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Three Software Stacks Required for IoT Architectures</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/white-papers/iot-architectures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/white-papers/iot-architectures/</guid>
      <description>Introduction  The Internet of Things (IoT) is transforming how individuals and organizations connect with customers, suppliers, partners, and other individuals. IoT is all about connecting sensors, actuators, and devices to a network and enabling the collection, exchange, and analysis of generated information. Hardware innovations, like the Raspberry Pi, are making it easier, faster and cheaper to develop new devices. Networking standards for low power networks, like LoRaWAN or NB-IOT, create new opportunities for connecting very small devices to a network.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>