<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eclipse IoT</title>
    <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eclipse IoT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://iot.eclipse.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT World 2017</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-20-iot-day-sanjose-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-20-iot-day-sanjose-2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hannover Messe 2017</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-04-24-hannover-messe-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-04-24-hannover-messe-2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devoxx US 2017</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-21-devoxxus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-21-devoxxus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Converge 2017</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-20-eclipse-converge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-20-eclipse-converge/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Day - San Jose</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-20-iot-world-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-20-iot-world-2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CEA List</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/cealist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/cealist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;List, expert on digital systems&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based in Saclay (Paris region, France), List is a public research institute specialized in digital systems design. Its main mission is based on achieving excellence technological development on behalf of industrial partners for value creation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;100 industrial collaborations per year&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;List institute counts more than 700 partners and every year more than a 100 partnership activities are being conducted with French and foreign industrial companies on applied research projects in four main topics:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced Manufacturing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Embedded systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ambient intelligence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health ionizing radiations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
Labeled as Carnot Institute , List invests every year 25% of its budget into scientific resourcing actions in order to identify better tomorrows technological breakthroughs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CEA Tech as CEA (Commissariat a l&amp;rsquo;energie atomique et aux energies alternatives) Technological Research Division, gathers three specialised technological research institutes among which List institute specialised on digital systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;At a world class state-of-the-art&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our activity is based on three main pillars
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;u&gt;Scientific excellence&lt;/u&gt;: List research engineers dedicate a 100% of their time to R&amp;amp;D activities and publish their results into international leading conferences and scientific journals. Keeping a strong link with academic research, they base their research on world-wide state of the art.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;u&gt;The Culture of Industry&lt;/u&gt;: Our research teams are enlightened and motivated by a results-driven culture of projects, fixing themselves clear objectives to reach within committed deadlines and budgets. Each project launched by List Institute is fully assigned to permanent and suited human resources. The project management is based on a precise calendar, identified milestones and a clear description of deliverables. Research results confidentiality and intellectual property (patents) are defined by the parties in the collaboration agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;u&gt;Opening to the world&lt;/u&gt;: List Institute is fully integrated into a local and national particularly dynamic ecosystem through strategic academic, institutional and industrial partnerships. In order to maintain the best level internationally in its fields of activity List institute is also involved in more than 200 European collaborative projects, collaborates with leading foreign academic laboratories and conducts research activities at an international level, especially in the USA.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Open IoT Challenge 3.0 Scholars!</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-12-06-iotchallenge-scholars/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-12-06-iotchallenge-scholars/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The third edition of the Open IoT Challenge officially started. More than 80 teams have submitted their entries and are now in the running to win the Open IoT Challenge 3.0! The judges have reviewed all submissions and we have awarded a “starter kit” to the most promising solutions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Data, Open Tools: Transforming IoT, LocationTech &amp; Science</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-11-24-meetup-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-11-24-meetup-london/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open IoT Challenge 3.0 | Deadline Extended!</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-11-24-iotchallenge-extension/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-11-24-iotchallenge-extension/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The submission deadline for the Open IoT Challenge 3.0 has been extended to November 30 @ 11:59 PM PT. We already received many great submissions, but wanted to give submitters more time. Don&amp;rsquo;t delay, submit today!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT World Europe 2016</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-11-20-iot-world-europe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-11-20-iot-world-europe/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung ARTIK</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/samsung/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/samsung/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Samsung and Eclipse&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an effort to strengthen our commitment to open source development, Samsung Semiconductor Inc. is proud to be a solution member of the Eclipse Foundation. In May 2015, Samsung announced the Samsung ARTIK Smart IoT platform in effort to provide an end-to-end solution to help accelerate the development of IoT solutions. Samsung ARTIK leverages many projects sponsored by the Eclipse Foundation IoT Working Group, including Mosquitto, Paho, KURA, Wakaama and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Samsung ARTIK&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Samsung ARTIK end-to-end, integrated platform unifies hardware, software, cloud, security, and a partner ecosystem in a single offering. ARTIK does the heavy lifting so you can focus on differentiating your products and services. Reduce costs, time and risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Within the platform, the Samsung ARTIK Cloud provides easy-to-use, open, and enterprise-grade APIs, SDKs, and tools in a single integrated platform. Companies can use these APIs, SDKs, and tools to collect, store, and act on any data from any device or cloud service, and speed up their product development process, accelerate time to market and revenue, and improve value to customers.
We specifically focus our activities on the openHAB project, but we are also promoting the ideals of Free software in general.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting Objects to the Cloud using Eclipse Leshan</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-11-16-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 16:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-11-16-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Internet of Things is rising fast, but how can it be run safely and efficiently using standards?  OMA Lightweight M2M is an IoT protocol for managing smart objects. It provides answers to the typi…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETSI IoT/M2M Workshop</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-11-14-etsi-iot-m2m-workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-11-14-etsi-iot-m2m-workshops/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>coap</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/standards/coap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 17:57:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/standards/coap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CoAP&lt;/strong&gt; (Constrained Application Protocol) is a protocol specialized for use with constrained nodes and networks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It implements the REST architectural style, it can be transparently mapped to HTTP. However, CoAP also provides features that go beyond HTTP such as native push notifications and group communication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;col-md-6&#34;&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;
      &lt;i class=&#34;icon-forward&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; Download a CoAP runtime
    &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
      The
      &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.eclipse.org/californium/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Eclipse Californium project&lt;/a&gt; provides a Java implementation of the CoAP protocol, including support for the DTLS security layer. The source code of Californium is available from the
      &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.eclipse.org/californium&#34;&gt;project webpage&lt;/a&gt;, and is also available from Maven Central.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;col-md-6&#34;&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;
      &lt;i class=&#34;icon-forward&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; CoAP Sandbox Server
    &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
      We provide a
      &lt;a href=&#34;sandbox.html#coap&#34;&gt;sandbox server&lt;/a&gt; that exposes some testing resources over CoAP. You can use it to test your CoAP communication scenarios.
    &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dtls</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/standards/dtls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 17:57:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/standards/dtls/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;
  The &lt;strong&gt;Datagram Transport Layer Security (DTLS)&lt;/strong&gt; protocol provides communications security for datagram protocols such as. DTLS allows datagram-based applications to communicate in a way that is designed to prevent eavesdropping, tampering, or message forgery. For IoT applications, DTLS can be used to secure CoAP-based communications.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;col-md-6&#34;&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;
      &lt;i class=&#34;icon-forward&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; Download a DTLS implementation
    &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The
      &lt;a href=&#34;https://eclipse.org/tinydtls&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Eclipse tinydtls project&lt;/a&gt; provides a light-weight implementation of the DTLS protocol that can be used in devices with tight memory constraints, i.e. in the order of 100 KiB flash memory and about 10 KiB RAM. You can
      &lt;a href=&#34;http://git.eclipse.org/c/tinydtls/org.eclipse.tinydtls.git&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;download tinydtls source code&lt;/a&gt; from the project&#39;s Git repository.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>