<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eclipse IoT</title>
    <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eclipse IoT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 10:48:55 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://iot.eclipse.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Asset Tracking</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/testbeds/asset-tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 10:48:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/testbeds/asset-tracking/</guid>
      <description>Leveraging Eclipse Kura for data acquisition and reliable connectivity The Eclipse Kura open source project is used to provide an easy-to-deploy edge computing stack that can run on virtually any IoT gateway device that would typically be found in airport baggage management systems or in a delivery truck.
It is used for communicating with Bluetooth low energy sensors that are attached to valuable parcels that need to be tracked. As Kura provides built-in support for Bluetooth communication, it provides a great starting point for interfacing with the sensors in order to collect data such as temperature, humidity, vibration, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Production Performance Management</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/testbeds/production-performance-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 16:54:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/testbeds/production-performance-management/</guid>
      <description>At the heart of the testbed is the Production Performance Management Protocol (PPMP), which allows uniform representation of all the data and information related to manufacturing processes. The testbed showcases how performance data from different industrial assets can be connected to the same IoT Cloud backend, so that this data can be further processed, or simply visualized.   Standardized communication using PPMP  PPMP specifies a format that allows to capture data that is required to do performance analysis of production facilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supporting Software Updates with Open Source IoT</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/case-studies/supporting-software-updates-with-open-source-iot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/case-studies/supporting-software-updates-with-open-source-iot/</guid>
      <description>Kynetics is a Software Development Company with offices in California and Italy. It was founded in 2006 and specializes in embedded and server-side technologies. Kynetics provides tools and services that feature an integrated and consistent Internet of Things (IoT) development software pipeline. The company provides software as a service (SaaS) that is reliable and resilient, built utilizing open source technologies to deploy software updates to IoT devices, along with a recovery system for safe measure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying IoT on Germany&#39;s DB Railway System</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/case-studies/iot-on-railway-systems-db/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/case-studies/iot-on-railway-systems-db/</guid>
      <description>Deutsche Bahn AG (DB), German Railway, is one of the largest transport and logistics companies in the world. DB Systel is DB&amp;rsquo;s internal Information and Communication Technology (ICT) partner, providing modern and efficient ICT products and services on the national and international level.&amp;nbsp;
The rail expertise of DB Systel covers the whole lifecycle of ICT solutions, from planning and development to operation and optimization. &amp;ldquo;Our goal is to be the company that integrates and enables digitalization at Deutsche Bahn,&amp;rdquo; says Alexander Schmitt, Chief Architect at DB Systel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Propose a new testbed</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/testbeds/propose-a-new-testbed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/testbeds/propose-a-new-testbed/</guid>
      <description>The Eclipse Open IoT Testbeds are an initiative of the Eclipse IoT Working Group. The testbeds focus on demonstrating how open source, open standards along with commercial solutions can be used to create real-world, industry specific IoT solutions.
If you are interested in proposing a new testbed, you can send an email to iot@eclipse.org. A proposal for a new testbed should include the following details:
 Short description of the scenario High-level architecture Identified extension points List of interested members List of applicable Eclipse IoT projects  In order to lead a testbed, your company needs to be a member of the Eclipse IoT Working Group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Things IoT @ EclipseCon Europe</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-10-22-iot-ece-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-10-22-iot-ece-2018/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EclipseCon France 2018</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-06-13-ecf-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-06-13-ecf-2018/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Day Santa Clara | Recorded Talks Available</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-05-30-iot-day-sc-talks-recorded/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-05-30-iot-day-sc-talks-recorded/</guid>
      <description>Couldn&amp;rsquo;t attend the Eclipse IoT Day Santa Clara in person? Watch the recording on YouTube!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cirrus Link</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/cirruslink/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/cirruslink/</guid>
      <description>Cirrus Link Solutions provide secure and reliable IIOT software solutions enabled with MQTT that integrates process information throughout the organization bridging the IT / OT gap while supplying a superior OT solution.
With over 30 years of SCADA and Telemetry experience and the co-inventor of MQTT where M2M and IoT started, Cirrus Links understands the technology requirements to help companies achieve their business objectives. Our experiences and ingenuity has been integral in developing the technology to enable and effectively manage data assets for real-time controls to big data analytics for AI and predictive maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Newsletter | May 2018</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-05-23-iot-newsletter-may/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-05-23-iot-newsletter-may/</guid>
      <description>Read the latest issue of the Eclipse IoT Newsletter, featuring Eclipse Keti, Eclipse Hono, MQTT 5 and more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fondazione Bruno Kessler - FBK</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/fbk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/fbk/</guid>
      <description>Fondazione Bruno Kessler - FBK - is a private no profit research institution based in Trento, Italy. FBK is divided in several centres and its mission is to develop both knowledge and expertise in the fields of Information and Communication Technology, Microsystems/Microelectronics and Social science, aiming to conduct technology transfer at the local, national and international industrial level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Day Santa Clara</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-05-14-iot-day-santa-clara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-05-14-iot-day-santa-clara/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT World 2018</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-04-14-iot-world-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-04-14-iot-world-2018/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KubeCon / CloudNativeCon Europe 2018</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-05-02-kubecon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-05-02-kubecon/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Developer Survey 2018 | Results are in</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-04-17-iot-surver-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-04-17-iot-surver-2018/</guid>
      <description>Results from the IoT Developer Survey are in! Read about the key findings about IoT cloud platforms, databases, security, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kynetics</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/kynetics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/kynetics/</guid>
      <description>Kynetics provides full software stacks for the most popular embedded application processors focussing in particular on NXP SoCs. In cooperation with hardware manufacturers, Kynetics has been working on popular embedded products tailoring operating systems Android and Linux based including applications for different industries. Quality of the artifacts is delivered through a continuous integration process from source code management, build and image deployment on target devices. Kynetics leverages a solid background in the development of microservices architectures, and provides to its customers full support to the pipeline of product development in the IoT space, which starts from edge devices and their embedded software stack test and delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winners of Open IoT Challenge 4.0 Demonstrate How Open Source Accelerates Innovation</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-04-04-iot-challenge4-winners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-04-04-iot-challenge4-winners/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re pleased to announce the winners of the fourth annual Open IoT Challenge! Thank you to the 78 teams who participated in this year&amp;rsquo;s Challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoTBuild</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-03-27-iotbuild/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-03-27-iotbuild/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activ-IoTy Timekeeping - Final Report</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activ-ioty-timekeeping---final-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activ-ioty-timekeeping---final-report/</guid>
      <description>Watch the video summarizing all the work done in this project in just 3 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alya-Smart-Mirror OpenIoTChallenge Final Report</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya-smart-mirror-openiotchallenge-final-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya-smart-mirror-openiotchallenge-final-report/</guid>
      <description>There are already many impressive open source smart-mirror projects out there but we wanted to achieve even more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aquaponics - Final Report</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/aquaponics---final-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/aquaponics---final-report/</guid>
      <description>In this system that we are going to set up, a water pump, powered by solar panels, will be used to transport the water with fish waste to the plants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autonomy of Things - Final Report</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/autonomy-of-things---final-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/autonomy-of-things---final-report/</guid>
      <description>Three months ago i took the chance to make a commitment — to realise an idea i had for years. Long before it became known as the Internet-Of-Things, i connected devices with wires and radio frequency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CISSOS - Final Report</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/cissos---final-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/cissos---final-report/</guid>
      <description>We wanted to investigate how open-source software from the Eclipse IoT community can be used to build a full (I)IoT solution-stack from sensor to visualization based on the classical three tier architecture for IoT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Oscilloscope - Final Report</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/cloud-oscilloscope---final-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/cloud-oscilloscope---final-report/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our journey to Open IoT Challenge by Eclipse! Last December our proposal was chosen from 70 proposal to participate. Also we&amp;rsquo;ve got a promocode for electronics and started to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IIOT2K IoT Framework - Final Report</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/iiot2k-iot-framework---final-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/iiot2k-iot-framework---final-report/</guid>
      <description>I start to design and write the IIOT2K framework and share it with to you in conjunction with Eclipse IoT challenge 4.0. I hope that my framework helps IoT enthusiasts to realize there IoT projects in easily way. I would happy for suggestions for this project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MoDeS3 - The Smart City - Final Report</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/modes3---the-smart-city---final-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/modes3---the-smart-city---final-report/</guid>
      <description>We continued the MoDeS3 project (which won third place in 2016) and we built a smart city on top of the physical architecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenNMS - Final Report</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/opennms---final-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/opennms---final-report/</guid>
      <description>The aim of this project is to use IoT pollution measurements as a compelling use case to prove a design for an MQTT plugin for OpenNMS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poulpy - Final Report</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/poulpy---final-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/poulpy---final-report/</guid>
      <description>Poulpy was born with the intent of creating a connected aquarium network all over the country so people can monitor their aquariums and learn more about marine life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart solar water heating (SWH) - Final Report</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/smart-solar-water-heating-swh---final-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/smart-solar-water-heating-swh---final-report/</guid>
      <description>Smart solar water heating solution uses IoT and AI technologies to improve the efficiency of passive solar water heating system. This solution has been developed to take part in the Open IoT Challenge 4.0!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SmartOASYS - Final Report</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/smartoasys---final-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/smartoasys---final-report/</guid>
      <description>SmartOASYS is a dashboard for Water Monitoring system using IoT - PaaS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trusting IoT - Final Report</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---final-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---final-report/</guid>
      <description>n this post, we make a similar journey through our participation in the Eclipse Open IoT Challenge 4.0 with the project trusted indoor positioning system for nursing homes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trync - Final Report</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trync---final-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trync---final-report/</guid>
      <description>Here I&amp;rsquo;m going to write the worst final report for Open IoT Challenge 4.0 (may be the worst one in the Open IoT challenge history too 😞). Because than writing how we got success I&amp;rsquo;m writing here how we got failed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What about you (WAY) - Final Report</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/what-about-you-way---final-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/what-about-you-way---final-report/</guid>
      <description>What About You (WAY) is a project which has an IoT theme, a social &amp;amp; enjoyable characteristic and open source technologies. It focuses on informing people about each other’s mood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alya - Cloud voice recognition Alexa for alya-smart-mirror</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya---cloud-voice-recognition-alexa-for-alya-smart-mirror/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya---cloud-voice-recognition-alexa-for-alya-smart-mirror/</guid>
      <description>Alya can be integrated with Alexa using all the great built in capabilities of Alexa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alya - Offline gesture recognition for alya-smart-mirror</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya---offline-gesture-recognition-for-alya-smart-mirror/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya---offline-gesture-recognition-for-alya-smart-mirror/</guid>
      <description>Sensor hub is one of alya’s features collects and shows user’s various sensor hub such as temperature, humidity, light, face detections, face demographics and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alya - alya-smart-mirror as sensor hub for your home</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya---alya-smart-mirror-as-sensor-hub-for-your-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya---alya-smart-mirror-as-sensor-hub-for-your-home/</guid>
      <description>We will talk about the offline gesture recognition support of Aly. Now, Alya supports for now palm and fist gestures using Matrix creator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alya - asm-app: a react native mobile app to configure alya-smart-mirror</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya---asm-app-a-react-native-mobile-app-to-configure-alya-smart-mirror/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya---asm-app-a-react-native-mobile-app-to-configure-alya-smart-mirror/</guid>
      <description>Let’s introduce our react native app “asm app” which is one of the main alya core component. Our app plays a major role in our project as it’s an intermediary between the end user and the backend as discussed before in “asm-backend”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alya-Smart-Mirror from vision to reality</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya-smart-mirror-from-vision-to-reality/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya-smart-mirror-from-vision-to-reality/</guid>
      <description>What does the Alya-Smart-Mirror look like? Find out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Day Santa Clara | Speakers Announced</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-03-14-iot-sc-speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-03-14-iot-sc-speakers/</guid>
      <description>We are pleased to announce the speakers for the Eclipse IoT Day Santa Clara, co-located with IoT World 2018 on May 14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ModeS3 - DDS and Xtext</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/modes3---dds-and-xtext/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/modes3---dds-and-xtext/</guid>
      <description>Code generation from state machines to DDS execution environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ModeS3 - Our choice of DDS implementation: Vortex OpenSplice DDS</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/modes3---our-choice-of-dds-implementation-vortex-opensplice-dds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/modes3---our-choice-of-dds-implementation-vortex-opensplice-dds/</guid>
      <description>After we had decided to use DDS for the communication between the components of our distributed system that we would like to manage, we had to choose the implementation of this middleware.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trusting IoT - Testing: Four, five, six</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---testing-four-five-six/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---testing-four-five-six/</guid>
      <description>We commented on Testing: One, two, three, that we would like to develop a software tool which would allow anyone to fine-tune his/her installation to a position as accurately as possible. This tool is ready and available in mide repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trync - How we connect Eclipse Kura gateway to a web application hosted on WildFly</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trync---how-we-connect-eclipse-kura-gateway-to-a-web-application-hosted-on-wildfly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trync---how-we-connect-eclipse-kura-gateway-to-a-web-application-hosted-on-wildfly/</guid>
      <description>As we are using RaspberryPI hardware running Eclipse Kura on top of Raspbian OS as Trync gateway we have to connect it to the Trync Dashboad, a web application developed with Java hosted on WildFly application server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Oscilloscope - Build Scheme and components</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/cloud-oscilloscope---build-scheme-and-components/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/cloud-oscilloscope---build-scheme-and-components/</guid>
      <description>You need a number of components to assemble Cloud Oscilloscope. Most of them can be bought at the nearest radio store or on AliExpress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alya - Cloud-based Face Recognition for Alya Smart Mirror</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya---cloud-based-face-recognition-for-alya-smart-mirror/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya---cloud-based-face-recognition-for-alya-smart-mirror/</guid>
      <description>Alongside with the voice recognition support, Alya supports personalization through face recognition, in this article we will go through cloud-based face recognition in Alya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alya - Offline voice recognition for “alya-smart-mirror</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya---offline-voice-recognition-for-alya-smart-mirror/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya---offline-voice-recognition-for-alya-smart-mirror/</guid>
      <description>Having a voice recognition support in ASM is part of the core services which is used to recognize the voice commands given by the user. We selected an offline voice recognition service since it is less expensive and requires less configurations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ModeS3 - SmartCity Intro</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/modes3---smartcity-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/modes3---smartcity-intro/</guid>
      <description>MoDeS3 – Smart City project integrates these innovative solutions into a common framework and testbed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ActivIoTy - Checkpoints on the Move?</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activioty---checkpoints-on-the-move/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activioty---checkpoints-on-the-move/</guid>
      <description>We are on the last mile of the challenge, and I’m exploring new ways to enrich the user experience of the platform, adding new features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trusting IoT - Parallelizing IOTA transactions in Kura</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---parallelizing-iota-transactions-in-kura/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---parallelizing-iota-transactions-in-kura/</guid>
      <description>What’s the fuss about? From now on, Jura is scalable in terms of locations stored in the tangle. How? Using IOTA’s workers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autonomy of Things - Location Awareness in IoT with Beacon Technology</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/autonomy-of-things---location-awareness-in-iot-with-beacon-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/autonomy-of-things---location-awareness-in-iot-with-beacon-technology/</guid>
      <description>In this article I’ll share the findings of my feasibility tests for implementing a location service with Bluetooth beacon using iOS and Linux-powered devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Oscilloscope - Backend Architecture</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/cloud-oscilloscope---backend-architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/cloud-oscilloscope---backend-architecture/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re working on a backend for our Cloud Oscilloscope project. On the last meetings we decided to use common technologies for IoT to connect our device with backend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trusting IoT - The Race to the Tangle II: Teamwork</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---the-race-to-the-tangle-ii-teamwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---the-race-to-the-tangle-ii-teamwork/</guid>
      <description>This post is a continuation of the race to the tangle in which we discuss how we try to increase the number of transactions we make to the tangle with the hardware we have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nokia</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/nokia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/nokia/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trync - Installing and configuring Mosquitto MQTT broker</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trync---installing-and-configuring-mosquitto-mqtt-broker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trync---installing-and-configuring-mosquitto-mqtt-broker/</guid>
      <description>For communicating between Trync gateways (trync-g) and Trync main server we are using MQTT and we have chosen Mosquitto MQTT broker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trync - Installing and configuring WildFly application server with a Let&#39;s Encrypt SSL/TLS certificate</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trync---installing-and-configuring-wildfly-application-server-with-a-lets-encrypt-ssl/tls-certificate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trync---installing-and-configuring-wildfly-application-server-with-a-lets-encrypt-ssl/tls-certificate/</guid>
      <description>We are using WildFly application server for hosting Trync dashboard and its services written in Java. Following steps will describe how we configured WildFly on our DigitalOcean droplet running CentOS 7.4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trync - Server infrastructure for Trync</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trync---server-infrastructure-for-trync/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trync---server-infrastructure-for-trync/</guid>
      <description>For deploying Trync dashboard and services we have choose a DigitalOcean droplet running CentOS 7.4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trusting IoT - Testing: One, two, three</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---testing-one-two-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---testing-one-two-three/</guid>
      <description>This weekend we have met up in order to perform some experiments, and taking advantage of this meeting we are going to show you how to install Jura.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open IoT Challenge - 2 weeks to go!</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-03-02-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-03-02-challenge/</guid>
      <description>There are about 12 teams actively participating and blogging about their journey (and probably more that are working in “stealth mode”), so it&amp;rsquo;s time to highlight some of the really cool things they are working on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trusting IoT - Firma: In IOTA We Trust</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---firma-in-iota-we-trust/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---firma-in-iota-we-trust/</guid>
      <description>We are pleased to present Firma, the last part of Jura. “Firmar” is the Spanish word of the verb “to sign” and the translation of firma in English is &amp;ldquo;it signs&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ActivIoTy - The (Activ-IoTy) Controller</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activioty---the-activ-ioty-controller/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activioty---the-activ-ioty-controller/</guid>
      <description>The Controller is a MQTT subscriber that processes the checkins performed on Checkpoints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trusting IoT - Our Approach. Part II. Trusted IPS</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---our-approach.-part-ii.-trusted-ips/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---our-approach.-part-ii.-trusted-ips/</guid>
      <description>We have been waiting to post this for weeks. It is not because we are playing hard to get, we just wanted to see how far we could go :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trusting IoT - The Race to the Tangle</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---the-race-to-the-tangle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---the-race-to-the-tangle/</guid>
      <description>These days we are using the starter kit that we got for our proposal for the Eclipse Open IoT Challenge 4.0 to carry out different tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT cloud platform with EnMasse and Apache Spark using Red Hat OpenShift</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/iot-cloud-platform-with-enmasse-and-apache-spark-using-red-hat-openshift/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/iot-cloud-platform-with-enmasse-and-apache-spark-using-red-hat-openshift/</guid>
      <description>The server uses a computer with OpenShift to deploy EnMasse and Apache Spark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alya - A React component for getting YouTube videos using voice</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya---a-react-component-for-getting-youtube-videos-using-voice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya---a-react-component-for-getting-youtube-videos-using-voice/</guid>
      <description>A week ago, we have introduced our new project “Alya” in participation for Eclipse Open IoT Challenge , “Alya” is a modular personalized open-source smart mirror. In this blog, I am excited to talk about one of the core addons…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ActivIoTy - Implementation of Low-Cost Activ-IoTy Checkpoint in Python</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activioty---implementation-of-low-cost-activ-ioty-checkpoint-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activioty---implementation-of-low-cost-activ-ioty-checkpoint-in-python/</guid>
      <description>This solution only needs a bluetooth input device connected to a Raspberry Pi, or similar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bosch ConnectedWorld 2018</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-02-21-bcw-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-02-21-bcw-2018/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trusting IoT - Ubica: An Indoor Positioning System</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---ubica-an-indoor-positioning-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---ubica-an-indoor-positioning-system/</guid>
      <description>Ubicar is the Spanish word of the verb “to locate“. The translation of ubica in English is “it locates“. Ubica is another part of Jura and its function is to locate BLE beacons, hereinafter beacons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>V2COM</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/v2com/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/v2com/</guid>
      <description>With more than 12 years of Internet of Things (IoT) experience and more than one million devices connected world-wide, V2COM provides a platform to turn products into intelligent connected devices. V2COMs technology accelerates IoT project deployments and their time-to-market. V2COMs core offerings and products serve as an operating system that removes the complexity of data protocols, sensors interfaces, security, microprocessors architecture, software application language and wireless connectivity to create seamless, device intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ActivIoTy - IR Keypad on Arduino</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activioty---ir-keypad-on-arduino/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activioty---ir-keypad-on-arduino/</guid>
      <description>A system based on Infrared (IR) remote control, is not very reliable for our purpose since there must be a direct visual line between transmitter and receiver –likely TV remote controls. More than a real solution, this is a proof of concept.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trusting IoT - Graba: A BLE Beacons Recording System</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---graba-a-ble-beacons-recording-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---graba-a-ble-beacons-recording-system/</guid>
      <description>Grabar is the Spanish word of the verb &amp;ldquo;to record&amp;rdquo;. The translation of graba in English is “it records“. Graba is part of Jura and its function is to record datasets. It consists of two Kura’s plug-ins: iot.challenge.jura.graba and iot.challenge.jura.graba.web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“alya” a DIY modular personalized open-source smart mirror</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya-a-diy-modular-personalized-open-source-smart-mirror/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/alya-a-diy-modular-personalized-open-source-smart-mirror/</guid>
      <description>Two months has passed since the eclipse open IoT challenge 4.0 started, and in this first blog we are so excited to talk about our idea “alya-smart-mirror”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activ-IoTy Checkpoint: UHF RFID &#43; RPi &#43; Paho for Python</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activ-ioty-checkpoint-uhf-rfid---rpi---paho-for-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activ-ioty-checkpoint-uhf-rfid---rpi---paho-for-python/</guid>
      <description>One of the most important pieces of Activ-IoTy is Checkpoints. This article features the implementation of a checkpoint based on a IND903 UHF RFID Reader, connected to a Raspberry Pi (or a Intel Up Squared).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trusting IoT - Faro: A Multimodal BLE Beacon</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---faro-a-multimodal-ble-beacon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---faro-a-multimodal-ble-beacon/</guid>
      <description>Faro is the Spanish term for a lighthouse, as well as a multimodal Bluetooth Low Energy Beacon service for Eclipse Kura.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jfokus 2018</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-02-05-jfokus-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-02-05-jfokus-2018/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2018</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-02-03-fosdem-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-02-03-fosdem-2018/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trusting IoT - Building Deployment Packages for Eclipse Kura</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---building-deployment-packages-for-eclipse-kura/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---building-deployment-packages-for-eclipse-kura/</guid>
      <description>OSGi is ideal for managing IoT gateways and we believe that it is a wise move that Eclipse Kura has been developed using it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Things Conference</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-02-01-the-things-network-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2018-02-01-the-things-network-conference/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart solar water heating (SWH) - IoT gateway with Raspberry Pi using Eclipse Kura</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/smart-solar-water-heating-swh---iot-gateway-with-raspberry-pi-using-eclipse-kura/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/smart-solar-water-heating-swh---iot-gateway-with-raspberry-pi-using-eclipse-kura/</guid>
      <description>The gateway uses a Raspberry Pi with Eclipse Kura to run the application that controls the relay board, Eclipse Leshan to communicate with the sensor, and Eclipse Paho to communicate with the server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activ-IoTy - new Video</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activ-ioty---new-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activ-ioty---new-video/</guid>
      <description>High level explanation of the objectives of Activ-IoTy, a personal project being developed for the Open IoT Challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activ-IoTy - MQTT: Cornerstone of Activ-IoTy</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activ-ioty---mqtt-cornerstone-of-activ-ioty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activ-ioty---mqtt-cornerstone-of-activ-ioty/</guid>
      <description>Activ-IoTy is based on the pub-sub paradigm. This means that some components (publishers or senders) send messages to a central point, called broker, that delivers the messages to other components (subscribers or receivers) interested in receiving the information send by the publishers…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trusting IoT - Preliminary results</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---preliminary-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusting-iot---preliminary-results/</guid>
      <description>This has been a great week for us :). Our team consists of three computer engineers; all of us from different fields, with great interest and curiosity about IoT but inexperienced in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lauching IoT Developer Survey 2018</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-01-24-iot-survey-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-01-24-iot-survey-2018/</guid>
      <description>We just launched the fourth IoT Developer Survey in partnership with IEEE IoT Initiative, the Open Mobile Alliance, and the AGILE-IoT. Please take 10 short minutes to complete the survey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CISSOS - Getting started with the Open IoT Challenge!</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/cissos---getting-started-with-the-open-iot-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/cissos---getting-started-with-the-open-iot-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Two months have passed since we handed in our topic for the Open IoT Challenge and now we (finally!) want to give an introduction to our project and what we want to (and have already) achieve(d).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protocol Layers of Activ-IoTy</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/protocol-layers-of-activ-ioty/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/protocol-layers-of-activ-ioty/</guid>
      <description>ActivIoTy is based on recognized standard protocols. Since the platform is designed to allow different and heterogeneous devices and implementations, standard technologies are crucial for scalability, enhancement of the system, and also to preserve integrity of data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trync - Setup development environment for ESP32 - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trync---setup-development-environment-for-esp32---part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trync---setup-development-environment-for-esp32---part-2/</guid>
      <description>In the first part we have already setup and configured ESP-IDF. So let&amp;rsquo;s do the code, compile and flash with an IDE. I have choose Eclipse IDE which is my favorite for a long time for Java, Atmel AVR and now ESP32 developments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activ-IoTy Components</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activ-ioty-components/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activ-ioty-components/</guid>
      <description>Checkpoints and Controller: these are the main pieces of ActivIoTy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trync - Setup development environment for ESP32 - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trync---setup-development-environment-for-esp32---part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trync---setup-development-environment-for-esp32---part-1/</guid>
      <description>For Trync hardware development the key component (Trync agent or Trync-a in short) is ESP32 SoC microcontroller by Espressif.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Newsletter - January 2018</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-01-18-iot-newsletter-jan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-01-18-iot-newsletter-jan/</guid>
      <description>The latest newsletter is available! It features articles about, Eclipse Cyclone, Eclipse Kura, Eclipse hono, IoT APIs, cloud-native IoT, and IoT trends in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Day Santa Clara</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-01-15-iot-day-santa-clara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-01-15-iot-day-santa-clara/</guid>
      <description>We are happy to announce the upcoming Eclipse IoT Day Santa Clara on May 14, 2018, in co-location with IoT World 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hardware solutions for Eclipse IOT Challenge: Exploring LoRa/LoRaWAN</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/hardware-solutions-for-eclipse-iot-challenge-exploring-lora/lorawan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/hardware-solutions-for-eclipse-iot-challenge-exploring-lora/lorawan/</guid>
      <description>The Open IoT challenge lead me to research more in depth different technologies both from the hardware and the software aspect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activ-IoTy at a Glance</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activ-ioty-at-a-glance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activ-ioty-at-a-glance/</guid>
      <description>ActivIoTy is a project, part of the Eclipse Open IoT Challenge 4.0 aiming at enhancing sports timekeeping systems, through IoT low-cost devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open IoT Challenge 4.0 - Teams are blogging</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-01-12-challenge4-blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2018-01-12-challenge4-blogs/</guid>
      <description>Follow the journey of Open IoT Challenge teams as they build their open IoT solutions! Click to read their blogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Oscilloscope - Meet the team</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/cloud-oscilloscope---meet-the-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/cloud-oscilloscope---meet-the-team/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year! I would like to take an opportunity and introduce our team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activ-IoTy - Sports Timekeeping &#43; IoT for Eclipse Challenge</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activ-ioty---sports-timekeeping---iot-for-eclipse-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/activ-ioty---sports-timekeeping---iot-for-eclipse-challenge/</guid>
      <description>To make running attractive among runners there are two important aspects to take into account: accurate/official timekeeping, and publication of comparable results for statistics and competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart solar water heating (SWH) - IoT temperature sensor with ESP8266 using LWM2M (Eclipse Wakaama)</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/smart-solar-water-heating-swh---iot-temperature-sensor-with-esp8266-using-lwm2m-eclipse-wakaama/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/smart-solar-water-heating-swh---iot-temperature-sensor-with-esp8266-using-lwm2m-eclipse-wakaama/</guid>
      <description>The sensor uses an ESP8266 board with the protocol Lightweight M2M to communicate the temperature read by DS18B20 to the gateway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart solar water heating (SWH) - Build an Android app to control a Q7 Camera P2P WIFI</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/smart-solar-water-heating-swh---build-an-android-app-to-control-a-q7-camera-p2p-wifi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/smart-solar-water-heating-swh---build-an-android-app-to-control-a-q7-camera-p2p-wifi/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial will teach you how to build an Android app to control a Q7 Camera P2P WIFI using the Android Studio development environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart solar water heating (SWH) - Connect wan automatically at boot and after a disconnection on OpenWrt</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/smart-solar-water-heating-swh---connect-wan-automatically-at-boot-and-after-a-disconnection-on-openwrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/smart-solar-water-heating-swh---connect-wan-automatically-at-boot-and-after-a-disconnection-on-openwrt/</guid>
      <description>OpenWrt is an open source project for embedded operating system based on Linux, primarily used on embedded devices to route network traffic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Oscilloscope - Top 12</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/cloud-oscilloscope---top-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/cloud-oscilloscope---top-12/</guid>
      <description>We have became a TOP-12 Proposal at Eclipse Open IoT Challenge! Thanks to everyone who believed in us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>little brother - Update</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/little-brother---update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/little-brother---update/</guid>
      <description>“little brother” runs in two language VM’s on the Raspberry PI. The first, Pharo, I’ve discussed at some length. The second I haven’t, partly because it’s better known, but partly because the use case has become clearer during development. It is the Java VM, specifically used with OSGi in the form of Eclipse Kura.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autonomy of Things</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/autonomy-of-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/autonomy-of-things/</guid>
      <description>Introducing an approach to create IoT solutions that base their functionality on momentarly available devices and resources, and do not rely on a fixed cloud provider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KubeCon</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-12-06-kubecon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-12-06-kubecon/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open IoT Challenge 4.0 - Top 12</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-12-06-challenge4-top12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-12-06-challenge4-top12/</guid>
      <description>The jury has deliberated and the Top 12 proposals for the fourth Open IoT Challenge have been announced! Congratulations to the top 12 teams and good luck to all 78 teams in building their solution to win the final prize.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trusted IoT - Our Approach</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusted-iot---our-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/trusted-iot---our-approach/</guid>
      <description>For the Open IoT Challenge 4.0 we propose a “trusted indoor positioning system for nursing homes” but, first of all, it is necessary to ask ourselves, do we know what is this?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Oscilloscope - Update 1</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/cloud-oscilloscope---update-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/cloud-oscilloscope---update-1/</guid>
      <description>Recently we&amp;rsquo;ve improved qt program on orange pi, now we can handle and show correct signal on display.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solar Logger - smaDataLogger Github</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/solar-logger---smadatalogger-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/solar-logger---smadatalogger-github/</guid>
      <description>View the Solar Logger GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solar Logger - Overview</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/solar-logger---overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/solar-logger---overview/</guid>
      <description>This Graphic gives an technical Overview to the Solar Data Logger Project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JVM-Con</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-11-28-jvmcon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-11-28-jvmcon/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>little brother - Pharo Smalltalk Resource Usage</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/little-brother---pharo-smalltalk-resource-usage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/little-brother---pharo-smalltalk-resource-usage/</guid>
      <description>One of the reasons for using Pharo, aside from the ease of controlling the hardware via object representations down to the pin level, is the relatively low resource usage compared with other IoT environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>little brother - Analysis Tools</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/little-brother---analysis-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/little-brother---analysis-tools/</guid>
      <description>To understand how the query, analysis and visualization tools work, a short overview of the Pharo Smalltalk environment in which they run is necessary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>little brother - Base Features</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/little-brother---base-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/little-brother---base-features/</guid>
      <description>What are the base features of “little brother”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>little brother - Difficulties</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/little-brother---difficulties/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/little-brother---difficulties/</guid>
      <description>Here are some of the main difficulties in completing the “little brother” infrastructure analysis IoT Initiative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is PharoThings?</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/what-is-pharothings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/what-is-pharothings/</guid>
      <description>PharoThings: a live programming IoT-platform</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Day Italy</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-11-24-iot-day-italy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-11-24-iot-day-italy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>little brother IoT</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/little-brother-iot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/little-brother-iot/</guid>
      <description>The core notion behind “little brother” is to overcome the inevitable lag between the increase in data volume and increases in available bandwidth and centralized processing power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacking Climate Change</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-11-18-hack-climate-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-11-18-hack-climate-change/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Cloud Oscilloscope</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/open-source-cloud-oscilloscope/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/open-source-cloud-oscilloscope/</guid>
      <description>This is a short story about our Cloud Oscilloscope or why should we be in Top 10 proposals at Open IoT Challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open IoT Challenge 4.0 - Deadline Extended</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-11-14-challenge4-deadline-extended/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-11-14-challenge4-deadline-extended/</guid>
      <description>We received so many great solution proposals that we decided to give you one more week to propose your solution! New deadline for submissions is November 20.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enter the Open IoT Challenge 4.0: Some ideas for your submission</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-11-03-challenge4-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-11-03-challenge4-ideas/</guid>
      <description>Get inspired by Benjamin&amp;rsquo;s ideas (deep learning, industrial IoT, blockchain and distributed ledgers, Low-power &amp;amp; long-life, &amp;hellip;) and enter this year&amp;rsquo;s Challenge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart solar water heating (SWH) - Intro</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/smart-solar-water-heating-swh---intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/entries/smart-solar-water-heating-swh---intro/</guid>
      <description>Smart solar water heating solution to take part in the Open IoT Challenge 4.0!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EclipseCon Europe 2017</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-10-24-eclipsecon-europe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-10-24-eclipsecon-europe/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Day @ EclipseCon Europe</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-10-23-eclipse-iot-ece/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-10-23-eclipse-iot-ece/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ADLINK Technology Inc.</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/adlink/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/adlink/</guid>
      <description>ADLINK is ‘Leading EDGE COMPUTING’ by delivering the network nodes that enable practical and scalable IoT systems. Building on its strong heritage in embedded computing, ADLINK provides the hardware and advanced Edge-aware software capabilities necessary for the multi-vendor, multi-standard connectivity required in end-to-end IT/OT business solutions. ADLINK reduces the complexity and helps speed the deployment of enterprise IoT systems that liberate data from vendor silos and other islands-of-automation, thus enabling business improvement in terms of operational excellence, enhanced customer service and support for new business models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orange</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/orange/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/orange/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InfluxData</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/influxdata/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/influxdata/</guid>
      <description>At InfluxData, we see the state of time-based data and have a strong vision about how to move forward — a vision born of our authentic experiences and a conviction that drives us to be the modern engine propelling next-generation systems: a platform that empowers builders to create great things as this data revolution unfolds.
We are singularly focused on reducing the Time to Awesome ™, we truly care about helping developers and businesses get to results faster with less complexity and less code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Open IoT Testbed - Production Performance Management</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-10-19-industry40-testbed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-10-19-industry40-testbed/</guid>
      <description>We are pleased to announce a new Open IoT Testbed for Industry 4.0 focusing on Performance Monitoring Management in manufacturing. It’s been developed jointly by Bosch Software Innovations, CONTACT Software, Eurotech, fortiss GmbH, and InfluxData!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Paper: Open Source Software for Industry 4.0</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-10-19-industry40-whitepaper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-10-19-industry40-whitepaper/</guid>
      <description>Read the latest white paper created by the Eclipse IoT community to learn more about how open source software can be used to implement Industry 4.0 solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open IoT Challenge 4.0 - Video</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-10-12-challenge4-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 15:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-10-12-challenge4-video/</guid>
      <description>Work on things that matter and submit your open IoT solution idea for the fourth Open IoT Challenge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Newsletter - First Issue Published</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-10-12-iot-newsletter-oct/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-10-12-iot-newsletter-oct/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday we published the first issue of the new Eclipse IoT Newsletter! Thank you to the authors for contributing such great articles. Subscribe here to receive the next one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Hono – Eclipse Hono : Connect. Command. Control.</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-10-11-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 15:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-10-11-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>The open source response to closed and proprietary IoT solutions is called Eclipse Hono!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Case Study: Supporting Software Updates with Open Source IoT</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-10-11-case-study-kynetics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-10-11-case-study-kynetics/</guid>
      <description>We worked with Kynetics to create this case study featuring their use of Eclipse hawkBit to support IoT software updates!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Software for Industry 4.0</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/white-papers/2017-10-19-industry40/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/white-papers/2017-10-19-industry40/</guid>
      <description>The purpose of this white paper is to identify the types of software required to implement an Industry 4.0 solution. Software is a key enabling technology for any IoT solution, including IoT in manufacturing. This white paper investigates how software solutions can be used to integrate existing operational technologies on a factory floor with the existing enterprise applications, like PLM and ERP solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Solutions World Congress</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-10-03-iot-world-congress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-10-03-iot-world-congress/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lauching Open IoT Challenge 4.0</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-09-28-challenge4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-09-28-challenge4/</guid>
      <description>Build an awesome and innovative open IoT solution and you could win the fourth Open IoT Challenge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Things IoT @ EclipseCon Europe</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-09-27-all-things-iot-ece/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-09-27-all-things-iot-ece/</guid>
      <description>There is so much IoT content and activities at EclipseCon Europe this year, we created a special guide for all of you IoT enthusiasts! We hope it helps you get the most out of your time that week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intel</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/intel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/intel/</guid>
      <description>Intel® Software helps developers to build innovative edge-to-cloud solutions with hardware, software, and data capabilities that make development easy, secure and scalable.
Visit the Intel® Software Developer Zone for IoT to gain access to our complete dev kits, tools, comprehensive code libraries, SDKs, technical content and support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Hackathon Singapore</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-09-25-iot-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-09-25-iot-hackathon/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thingmonk 2017</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-09-12-thingmonk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-09-12-thingmonk/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Day @ Thingmonk</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-09-11-eclipse-thingmonk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-09-11-eclipse-thingmonk/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT @ EclipseCon Europe</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-09-05-iot-ece-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-09-05-iot-ece-program/</guid>
      <description>The program for the Eclipse IoT Day @ EclipseCon Europe (Oct 24) is now available. Join us for the many IoT events co-located with EclipseCon Europe, including the Smart Home Day, the Eclipse IoT Working Group Meeting, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudera</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/cloudera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 15:31:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/cloudera/</guid>
      <description>Cloudera delivers the modern platform for machine learning and advanced analytics built on the latest open source technologies. The world&amp;rsquo;s leading organizations trust Cloudera to help solve their most challenging business problems by efficiently capturing, storing, processing and analyzing vast amounts of data.
Cloudera was founded in 2008 by some of the brightest minds at Silicon Valleys leading companies including Google (Christophe Bisciglia), Yahoo! (Amr Awadallah), Oracle (Mike Olson), and Facebook (Jeff Hammerbacher).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lauching Eclipse IoT Newsletter</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-08-04-iot-newsletter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-08-04-iot-newsletter/</guid>
      <description>Great news! We are lauching a quartely Eclipse IoT Newsletter. The first issue will be sent at the end of September. Subcribe to the list to stay up-to-date about everything Eclipse IoT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Unide – A way to establish an open Industry 4.0 standard</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-08-02-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 15:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-08-02-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>With Industry 4.0 and Smart Manufacturing the need of communication and interoperability of machines and the Internet of Things (IoT) became bigger and bigger …</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Day @ ThingMonk</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-08-01-thingmonk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-08-01-thingmonk/</guid>
      <description>We are hosting the second Eclipse IoT Day in London, UK on September 11. We are pleased to co-locate with ThingMonk (Sep 12-13) again this year. Check out the awesome speaker line-up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CONTACT Software</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/contact-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/contact-software/</guid>
      <description>CONTACT Software is a leading vendor of software for the product engineering process and the digital transformation.
We connect people, teams and companies. Our mission: Energizing great minds. Instead of rigid systems, we create a working world in which employees can concentrate their skills on providing better products and services. A working world in which collaboration runs more smoothly, processes become more efficient and routine work becomes easier. Our guiding framework provides both security and freedom allowing agile interaction between individuals and teams in complex projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rapid IoT Prototyping with Eclipse Vorto</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-06-28-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 15:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-06-28-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Eclipse Vorto focuses on the interoperability for integrating IoT devices into various IoT Platforms …</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EclipseCon France 2017</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-06-21-ecf2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-06-21-ecf2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Live Slam</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-06-21-iot-slam-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-06-21-iot-slam-live/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Day @ EclipseCon Europe</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-06-12-ece-2017-cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-06-12-ece-2017-cfp/</guid>
      <description>We are hosting the annual Eclipse IoT Day @ EclipseCon Europe on October 24! The call for papers is open. We know you have something awesome to talk about, so submit your talk!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/sap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/sap/</guid>
      <description>As a market leader in enterprise application and digital transformation software, SAP helps companies of all sizes and industries run better. From back office to boardroom, warehouse to storefront, desktop to mobile devices, SAP empowers people and organizations to work together more efficiently by utilizing cloud, analytics, machine learning, Big Data, IoT and other insights more effectively to stay ahead of the competition. SAP applications and open cloud platform services enable more than 296,000 customers in 190 countries to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and grow sustainably.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DB Systel</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/db-systel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/db-systel/</guid>
      <description>DB Systel is using MQTT for a large number of IoT use cases, utilizing Eclipse Paho and Eclipse Mosquitto. We want to actively promote open standards and openness to enable digital innovation in the logistics and transportation industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Case Study: Deploying IoT on Germany&#39;s DB Railway System</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-05-17-db-case-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-05-17-db-case-study/</guid>
      <description>We worked with Deutsche Bahn (DB) to create this great case study about how they uses Eclipse IoT technology on their German railway system!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT World 2017</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-05-16-iotworld2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-05-16-iotworld2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Open Testbed for Asset Tracking - Live Demo</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-05-09-testbed-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 15:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-05-09-testbed-demo/</guid>
      <description>Unveiling the first Eclipse IoT Open Testbed for Asset Tracking Management. Check out this short video to get the gist of the business case. More info on Open Testbeds: https://iot.eclipse.org/testbeds/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Open Testbed for Asset Tracking - Live Demo</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-05-09-testbed-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-05-09-testbed-demo/</guid>
      <description>At Red Hat Summit 2017 we unveiled the first Eclipse IoT Open Testbed for Asset Tracking Management. Check out this short video to get the gist of the business case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Hat Summit</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-05-02-redhatsummit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-05-02-redhatsummit/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Eclipse IoT Open Testbeds</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-04-27-testbeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-04-27-testbeds/</guid>
      <description>Today we are announcing the Eclipse IoT Open Testbeds, a new initiative for driving adoption of open source and open standards in the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Developer Trends - 2017 Edition</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-04-26-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 15:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-04-26-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Slides: https://www.slideshare.net/IanSkerrett/iot-developer-survey-2017 The IoT Developer Survey Results are in for 2017! We received a record of 713 responses this year. During the webinar, we will …</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hannover Messe 2017</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-04-24-hannover-messe-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-04-24-hannover-messe-2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kichwa Coders</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/kichwa-coders/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/kichwa-coders/</guid>
      <description>At Kichwa Coders we build cutting-edge developer tools for the Internet of Things. We have experience at every level of the IoT stack from cloud to low-level embedded devices. Our clients rate us highly for our focus on excellence in software development, and for our versatility and dynamism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Developer Trends 2017 Edition</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-04-19-iot-developer-survey-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-04-19-iot-developer-survey-2017/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this year, we conducted the third annual IoT Developer Survey in partnership with AGILE IoT, IEEE IoT, and the IoT Council. We&amp;rsquo;re pleased to announced that the results are now available! What has changed in IoT since 2016? Find out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Makes an Open IoT Developer Challenge 3.0 Winner!</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-04-13-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 14:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-04-13-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>The Open IoT Challenge is an annual challenge to promote the use of open source and open standards in IoT solutions. The winners of the third Challenge were recently announced and they will be joining…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Eclipse Hono enables device-related communication for the IoT</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-03-24-hono-boschsi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 17:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-03-24-hono-boschsi/</guid>
      <description>Connectivity is at the heart of IoT solutions. Devices (things) need to be connected to a backend component where the data and functionality of the devices is leveraged to provide some higher level business value.…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Newsletter - Internet of all the Things</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-03-23-eclipse-newsletter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-03-23-eclipse-newsletter/</guid>
      <description>This month, the Eclipse Newsletter is all about the Internet of Things (IoT). The articles feature various Eclipse IoT projects including, Eclipse Hono, Eclipse ioFog, Eclipse Kapua, and Eclipse Vorto.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devoxx US 2017</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-21-devoxxus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-21-devoxxus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Converge 2017</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-20-eclipse-converge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-20-eclipse-converge/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Day - San Jose</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-20-iot-day-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-20-iot-day-2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congratulations | Open IoT Challenge 3.0 Winners!</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-03-16-iotchallenge3-winners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-03-16-iotchallenge3-winners/</guid>
      <description>Congratulations to this year&amp;rsquo;s Open IoT Challenge winners! Find out which team had the best solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bosch Connected World 2017</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-15-boschconnectedworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-15-boschconnectedworld/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Call | Complete the IoT Developer Survey 2017</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-03-14-iotsurvey-lastcall/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-03-14-iotsurvey-lastcall/</guid>
      <description>This is your last chance to complete the IoT Developer Survey 2017. The survey will close on March 17 at 11:59 PM PDT. Participate now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Day Grenoble</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-09-iotdaygrenoble/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-09-iotdaygrenoble/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visually Developing Solutions for the IoT with Reactive Blocks</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-03-08-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 17:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-03-08-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Reactive Blocks is a visual model-driven development environment supporting formal model analysis, automated code generation, hierarchical modelling, and an extensive library of ready-to-use components for the Java platform.…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internet of Manufacturing</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-07-iotmanufacturing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-03-07-iotmanufacturing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Container World 2017</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-02-21-containerworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2017-02-21-containerworld/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developing IoT-enabled Distributed Real-time Control Apps with Eclipse 4diac</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-02-16-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 17:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-02-16-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Industry 4.0 requires more interconnected, decentralized, and autonomous control entities seamless interacting with each other and the cloud. However, current systems are either limited in their adapt…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Announces Support for OMA LightweightM2M 1.0 Device Management Standard</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-02-15-leshan-pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-02-15-leshan-pr/</guid>
      <description>We are pleased to announce the Eclipse Leshan open source project will support the newly ratified Open Mobile Alliance (OMA) LightweightM2M (LwM2M) 1.0 device management standard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Participate in the IoT Developer Survey 2017</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-02-07-iotsurvey2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-02-07-iotsurvey2017/</guid>
      <description>We are pleased to launch the third annual IoT Developer Survey. Complete the survey now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Minecraft-Smart-Home: Prototyping the Internet of Uncanny Things</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-01-31-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 16:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-01-31-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Software solutions and everyday objects are becoming increasingly &amp;ldquo;smarter&amp;rdquo;, take over more &amp;ldquo;responsibility&amp;rdquo; and know more and more about us and our intentions. But what does that mean for developers,…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Day San Jose - Program Announced</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-01-31-iotdayprogram/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-01-31-iotdayprogram/</guid>
      <description>The program for the Eclipse IoT Day in San Jose on March 20 is now availble! We&amp;rsquo;re very excited about this event and we hope to see you there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Smarter Eclipse IoT Greenhouse with Eclipse Vorto, Kura, Californium</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-01-26-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 17:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-01-26-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>The official Eclipse IoT tutorial uses Eclipse Kura, Paho and Californium together with a Raspberry Pi, a temperature and a humidity sensor to implement a simple IoT example based on Eclipse IoT proje…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open IoT Challenge 3.0 — Mid-point Update!</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-01-19-iotchallenge-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2017-01-19-iotchallenge-update/</guid>
      <description>The Challenge teams have been working really hard and have been blogging about their solutions. Here are some of the most active blogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a wireless sensor network using Bluetooth Low Energy, MQTT-SN, and the BBC micro:bit</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-01-16-mqtt-sn-ble-microbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 10:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-01-16-mqtt-sn-ble-microbit/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kura Wires - A Mashup in Eclipse Kura for Industry 4.0</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-01-12-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 17:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2017-01-12-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Slides:http://www.slideshare.net/eclipsekura/building-iot-mashups-for-industry-40-with-eclipse-kura-and-kura-wires Video recording of the demo part: https://s3.amazonaws.com/kura-resources/Webminar-re…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Day San Jose</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-12-19-iotdaysanjose/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-12-19-iotdaysanjose/</guid>
      <description>We excited to announce the Eclipse IoT Day San Jose 2017. The event will take place on March 20, in co-location with Eclipse Converge and Devoxx US. The agenda is packed with great speakers covering a wide range of IoT topics, from Industry 4.0 and fog computing for devices at the edge, to smart homes and more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CEA List</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/cealist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/cealist/</guid>
      <description>List, expert on digital systems
Based in Saclay (Paris region, France), List is a public research institute specialized in digital systems design. Its main mission is based on achieving excellence technological development on behalf of industrial partners for value creation.
100 industrial collaborations per year
List institute counts more than 700 partners and every year more than a 100 partnership activities are being conducted with French and foreign industrial companies on applied research projects in four main topics:  Advanced Manufacturing Embedded systems Ambient intelligence Health ionizing radiations  Labeled as Carnot Institute , List invests every year 25% of its budget into scientific resourcing actions in order to identify better tomorrows technological breakthroughs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Reasons Why Java Is The Best Platform For Developing IoT Applications</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-12-08-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 16:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-12-08-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>The Java platform has many merits that make it an obvious choice for developing IoT applications. In this webinar, we’ll walk through the top ten reasons why you would want to use Java and Zulu Java,…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Open IoT Challenge 3.0 Scholars!</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-12-06-iotchallenge-scholars/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-12-06-iotchallenge-scholars/</guid>
      <description>The third edition of the Open IoT Challenge officially started. More than 80 teams have submitted their entries and are now in the running to win the Open IoT Challenge 3.0! The judges have reviewed all submissions and we have awarded a “starter kit” to the most promising solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Data, Open Tools: Transforming IoT, LocationTech &amp; Science</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-11-24-meetup-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-11-24-meetup-london/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open IoT Challenge 3.0 | Deadline Extended!</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-11-24-iotchallenge-extension/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-11-24-iotchallenge-extension/</guid>
      <description>The submission deadline for the Open IoT Challenge 3.0 has been extended to November 30 @ 11:59 PM PT. We already received many great submissions, but wanted to give submitters more time. Don&amp;rsquo;t delay, submit today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT World Europe 2016</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-11-20-iot-world-europe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-11-20-iot-world-europe/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung ARTIK</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/samsung/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/samsung/</guid>
      <description>Samsung and Eclipse
In an effort to strengthen our commitment to open source development, Samsung Semiconductor Inc. is proud to be a solution member of the Eclipse Foundation. In May 2015, Samsung announced the Samsung ARTIK Smart IoT platform in effort to provide an end-to-end solution to help accelerate the development of IoT solutions. Samsung ARTIK leverages many projects sponsored by the Eclipse Foundation IoT Working Group, including Mosquitto, Paho, KURA, Wakaama and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting Objects to the Cloud using Eclipse Leshan</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-11-16-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 16:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-11-16-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>The Internet of Things is rising fast, but how can it be run safely and efficiently using standards? OMA Lightweight M2M is an IoT protocol for managing smart objects. It provides answers to the typi…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using MQTT and Eclipse Paho in Android Things</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-12-19-mqtt-android-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 16:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-12-19-mqtt-android-things/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETSI IoT/M2M Workshop</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-11-14-etsi-iot-m2m-workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-11-14-etsi-iot-m2m-workshops/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>coap</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/standards/coap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 17:57:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/standards/coap/</guid>
      <description>CoAP (Constrained Application Protocol) is a protocol specialized for use with constrained nodes and networks.
It implements the REST architectural style, it can be transparently mapped to HTTP. However, CoAP also provides features that go beyond HTTP such as native push notifications and group communication.
  Download a CoAP runtime   The Eclipse Californium project provides a Java implementation of the CoAP protocol, including support for the DTLS security layer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dtls</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/standards/dtls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 17:57:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/standards/dtls/</guid>
      <description>The Datagram Transport Layer Security (DTLS) protocol provides communications security for datagram protocols such as. DTLS allows datagram-based applications to communicate in a way that is designed to prevent eavesdropping, tampering, or message forgery. For IoT applications, DTLS can be used to secure CoAP-based communications.   Download a DTLS implementation  The Eclipse tinydtls project provides a light-weight implementation of the DTLS protocol that can be used in devices with tight memory constraints, i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iec-61499</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/standards/iec-61499/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 17:57:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/standards/iec-61499/</guid>
      <description>The international standard IEC 61499, addressing the topic of function blocks for industrial process measurement and control system. The specification of IEC 61499 defines a generic model for distributed control systems and is based on the IEC 61131 standard.   Download an IEC-61499 toolset and runtime  The Eclipse 4DIAC project provides an industrial-grade open source infrastructure for distributed Industrial Process Measurement and Control Systems (IPMCS) based on the IEC 61499 standard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lwm2m</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/standards/lwm2m/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 17:57:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/standards/lwm2m/</guid>
      <description>OMA LightweightM2M (LWM2M) is an industry standard for device management of M2M/IoT devices. It heavily relies on CoAP and therefore is optimized for communications over sensor or cellular networks.  OMA LWM2M provides an extensible object model that allows to enable application data exchanges in addition to the core device management features (firmware upgrade, connectivity monitoring, &amp;hellip;)   Download a LWM2M runtime   The Eclipse Wakaama project provides a C portable framework for building LWM2M clients and/or servers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mqtt</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/standards/mqtt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 17:57:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/standards/mqtt/</guid>
      <description>MQTT is a protocol designed to connect the physical world devices and networks, with applications and middleware used in IT and Web development, making it an ideal connectivity protocol for IoT and M2M. It is a lightweight publish-subscribe protocol that runs on embedded devices and mobile platforms, while connecting to highly scalable enterprise and web servers over wired and wireless networks. It is useful for connections with remote embedded systems where a small code footprint is required and/or network bandwidth is at a premium or connectivity unpredictable, and, for mobile applications that require small size, low power usage, minimised data packets, and efficient distribution of information to one or many receivers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ogc-sensorthings-api</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/standards/ogc-sensorthings-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 17:57:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/standards/ogc-sensorthings-api/</guid>
      <description>SensorThings API is an Open Geospatial Consortium (OGC) standard providing an open and unified framework to interconnect IoT sensing devices, data, and applications over the Web. It is an open standard addressing the syntactic interoperability and semantic interoperability of the Internet of Things.   Download a SensorThings API runtime   The Eclipse Whiskers project provides a JavaScript client and a light-weight server for IoT gateways. The source code of Whiskers is available on the project&#39;s Github repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>onem2m</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/standards/onem2m/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 17:57:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/standards/onem2m/</guid>
      <description>oneM2M specifications provide a horizontal framework to support a wide range of applications and services such as smart cities, smart grid, connected car, home automation, public safety, and health.
  Download a oneM2M stack  The Eclipse OM2M project provides a Java implementation of the ETSI oneM2M. It provides a horizontal M2M service platform for developing services independently of the underlying network, with the aim to facilitate the deployment of vertical applications on heterogeneous devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>opc-ua</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/standards/opc-ua/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 17:57:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/standards/opc-ua/</guid>
      <description>OPC Unified Architecture (UA) is an interoperability standard that enables the secure and reliable exchange of industrial automation data while remaining cross-platform and vendor neutral. The specification is developed and maintained by the OPC Foundation with the guidance of individual software developers, industry vendors, and end-users. It defines the interface between Clients and Servers, including access to real-time data, monitoring of alarms and events, historical data access, and data modeling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ppmp</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/standards/ppmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 17:57:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/standards/ppmp/</guid>
      <description>PPMP (Production Performance Management Protocol) specifies a format that allows to capture data that is required to do performance analysis of production facilities. It allows monitoring backends to collect and evaluate key metrics of machines in the context of a production process. It is doing that by allowing to relate the machine status with currently produced parts.   Download a PPMP runtime   The Eclipse Unide project publishes the current version of PPMP and develops simple server/client implementations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fortiss GmbH</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/fortiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/fortiss/</guid>
      <description>fortiss is an institute associated with the Technical University of Munich and as such a full-fledged academic research institute while enjoying the independence granted by its legal form as a non-profit organization. Our mandate is to facilitate research and technology transfer in software-intensive systems and services, thereby triggering future ready innovation, with a focus on Bavaria. In this role fortiss acts as a technological think tank, bridging the notorious gap between fundamental research in academia and its fruitful implementation in an industrially and commercially feasible context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EclipseSource</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/eclipsesource/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/eclipsesource/</guid>
      <description>EclipseSource is a leader in Eclipse technology and provides you with the expertise to solve your domain challenges. Therefore, we create and adopt innovative as well as proven technology including all essential Eclipse frameworks.
EclipseSource is focused on Business Applications, Mobile Applications, Modeling Tools and Frameworks/Developer Tooling. We provide a complete range of services including conception, evaluation, training, support, consulting/implementation with a special focus on framework adoption, creation and maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eclipse edje</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/devices/eclipse-edje/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 14:48:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/devices/eclipse-edje/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open IoT Challenge 3.0 | Deadline is this Friday!</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-10-31-iotchallenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-10-31-iotchallenge/</guid>
      <description>This is your chance to demonstrate what you can build for the Internet of Things using open standards and open source technology! Submit your solution proposal by this Friday, November 25, 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EclipseCon Europe 2016</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-10-25-eclipsecon-europe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-10-25-eclipsecon-europe/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Day @ EclipseCon Europe</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-10-25-iot-day-ece/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-10-25-iot-day-ece/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IncQuery Labs Ltd.</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/incquery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 15:31:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/incquery/</guid>
      <description>IncQuery Labs Ltd. is a young and innovative company, founded in 2013 by a group of experts, with over 50 years of total R&amp;amp;D experience in model driven engineering. Our mission is to accelerate technology transfer from top-notch academic research to challenging industrial projects. We offer innovative R&amp;amp;D solutions like:
 high performance modeling tools with innovative traceability support, code generators and transformation chains (both batch and incremental), tool and runtime development for critical embedded and cyber-physical systems, superscalable queries for big data apps, and event and stream processing for IoT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Microservices at the Edge with Eclipse ioFog</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-10-20-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 17:03:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-10-20-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>There are many great ways to build IoT software in the cloud. And there are many great ways to store and analyze the large amounts of data produced by sensors and devices. Yet there are few ways to bu…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women in IoT meetup</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-10-19-women-in-iot-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-10-19-women-in-iot-meetup/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Three Software Stacks Required for IoT Architectures</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-10-14-white-paper-iot-architectures/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-10-14-white-paper-iot-architectures/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Three Software Stacks Required for IoT Architectures</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/white-papers/2016-10-01-iot-architectures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/white-papers/2016-10-01-iot-architectures/</guid>
      <description>In this white paper we look at the new technology requirements and architectures required for IoT solutions. It identifies three stacks of software required by any IoT solution and presents how open source communities, such as the Eclipse IoT community, are already supplying the critical software technology needed by IoT solution providers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything IoT @ EclipseCon Europe</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-09-29-iotece/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-09-29-iotece/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t miss all the IoT events at EclipseCon Europe taking place Oct 24-27 in Ludwigsburg, Germany. The conference includes an IoT Working Group meeting, IoT Day filled with great speakers/talks, IoT Playground and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT613</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-09-29-iot-613/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-09-29-iot-613/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Edje: A Java API for Microcontrollers</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-09-28-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 15:58:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-09-28-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Slides available at: http://www.slideshare.net/MicroEJ/eclipse-edje-a-java-api-for-microcontrollers-66604372
The Eclipse Edje project defines a standard high-level Java API called Hardware Abstractio…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Summit London</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-09-21-smartsummituk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-09-21-smartsummituk/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaOne 2016</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-09-18-javaone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-09-18-javaone/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Workshop: Get Started with the Open IoT - Women Who Code</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-09-14-iotworkshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-09-14-iotworkshop/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ThingMonk &#43; Eclipse IoT</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-09-12-thingmonk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-09-12-thingmonk/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IOTRACKS</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/iotracks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 15:31:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/iotracks/</guid>
      <description>With IOTRACKS fog computing, developing for the edge becomes as easy as developing for the Web.
 ioFabric gives you a universal runtime for the edge ComSat lets you interconnect private locations using the public Internet ioAuthoring gives you drag-and-drop microservices  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Summit London</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-08-08-smartsummit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-08-08-smartsummit/</guid>
      <description>This year, Tracy Miranda will be representing Eclipse IoT and open source at the Smart Summit in London on Sept 21-22. Planning to attend? Be sure to sit in on her panel!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to IoTivity</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-08-03-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 16:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-08-03-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>IoTivity is an open source implementation of the standards and specifications provided by the Open Connectivity Foundation. It is a communications framework for the Internet of Things that provides am…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Day @ Thingmonk</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-07-27-thingmonk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-07-27-thingmonk/</guid>
      <description>A new addition for Thingmonk this year is the Eclipse IoT Day @ Thingmonk on Day 0. We are planning an equally awesome line-up of speakers that will showcase how open source and Eclipse IoT has changing the IoT industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GetD</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-07-22-get-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-07-22-get-d/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Ecological Houses with Open Source and IoT</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-07-20-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 16:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-07-20-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Open Building Institute (OBI) was launched to make affordable, ecological housing accessible to everyone—using a library of engineered modules and a series of rapid-build procedures. We are developing…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with a W3C Web of Things Project</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-06-16-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 16:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-06-16-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>The W3C Web of Things (WoT) Interest Group (IG) is designing technological building blocks that help to complement existing IoT platforms and protocols, and thereby enable interoperability at a Web sc…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Eclipse IoT project releases to accelerate IoT solution development</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-06-16-new-project-releases/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-06-16-new-project-releases/</guid>
      <description>The Eclipse Internet of Things (IoT) Working Group, hosted at the Eclipse Foundation, is pleased to announce new releases for four open source IoT projects: Eclipse Kura 2.0, Eclipse Paho 1.2, Eclipse SmartHome 0.8 and Eclipse OM2M 1.0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EclipseCon France 2016</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-06-07-eclipseconfrance2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-06-07-eclipseconfrance2016/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concierge - Bringing OSGi (back) to Embedded Devices</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-06-02-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2016 16:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-06-02-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>The OSGi specifications provide a set of open standards describing a dynamic module system for the Java language which greatly facilitates the development of complex modular applications.The Eclipse C…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT DevCon</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-05-25-iot-devcon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-05-25-iot-devcon/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Updates in IoT with Eclipse hawkBit</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-05-18-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2016 15:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-05-18-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Updating software (components) on constrained edge devices as well as more powerful controllers and gateways is a common requirement in most IoT scenarios.
However, rolling out software updates in an…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSCON 2016</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-05-18-oscon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-05-18-oscon/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT - A Simple Overview</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-05-17-iot-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 19:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-05-17-iot-overview/</guid>
      <description>Eclipse IoT simplifies IoT developement. Learn all about Eclipse IoT by listening to this simple overview.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Things I learnt at IoT World 2016</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-05-16-learnt-iot-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-05-16-learnt-iot-world/</guid>
      <description>Discover the five things Benjamin Cabé learnt at IoT World 2016 last week!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT World</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-05-10-iot-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-05-10-iot-world/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PlatformIO: a cross-platform IoT solution to build them all!</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-05-05-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 16:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-05-05-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>PlatformIO is an open source environment for IoT development based on a cross-platform build system and a library manager. It&amp;rsquo;s simplifying continuous integration (including in the cloud!) of IoT syst…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Day Grenoble</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-04-28-iot-day-grenoble/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-04-28-iot-day-grenoble/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse NeoSCADA 0.3.0 released</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-04-28-neoscada-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-04-28-neoscada-release/</guid>
      <description>The Eclipse NeoSCADA team is proud to finally announce the 0.3.0 release!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Case Study 4DIAC: Smart Grid Automation (SGA) Software</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-04-27-case-study-noja/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-04-27-case-study-noja/</guid>
      <description>Read the latest case study and see how NOJA has adopted the Open Source Eclipse 4DIAC Framework for Industrial Automation and Control…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Grid Automation (SGA) Software</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/case-studies/smart-grid-automation-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/case-studies/smart-grid-automation-software/</guid>
      <description>NOJA Power (NOJA) researches, develops, manufactures and supplies low and medium voltage switchgear, specialising in auto reclosing circuit breakers for industrial, infrastructure and electricity distribution utilities.
NOJA&amp;rsquo;s signature product is the OSM series of medium-voltage (11kV and above) Automatic Circuit Reclosers (ACRs) which combine vacuum interruptors and solid dielectric insulation for switching, with state-of-the-art microelectronics for protection, SCADA and automation.
NOJA&amp;rsquo;s vision is to be the world leader in medium-voltage outdoor switchgear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can open source solve the too many IoT standards problem?</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-04-22-iot-standard-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-04-22-iot-standard-problems/</guid>
      <description>An important issue in the IoT industry is the plethora of IoT standards that exist today and new standards being created. The current situation for IoT standards has been described as…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spy on your MQTT devices for fun and profit with mqtt-spy</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-04-20-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-04-20-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>In this webinar +Kamil Baczkowicz will go through the key features of mqtt-spy, a JavaFX based application for MQTT/IoT developers, and explain how it can help you monitor and test your MQTT-based IoT…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Developer Survey Results Are In!</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-04-15-iot-developer-survey-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2016-04-15-iot-developer-survey-2016/</guid>
      <description>The results of our second annual IoT Developer Survey were released. They provide an interesting insight into how developers are building IoT solutions. Find out more…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIdO</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-04-07-sido/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-04-07-sido/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Summit</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-04-07-smart-summit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-04-07-smart-summit/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strong devices weakly connected: bringing DevOps to IoT with resin.io</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-04-06-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2016 15:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-04-06-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Web developers now enjoy a culture and set of tools that allow them to deploy software up to many times per day, quickly and safely. By contrast, much of the embedded world still operates on the annua…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenIoT Summit</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-04-06-openiot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-04-06-openiot/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Makes an Open IoT Developer Challenge Winner!</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-03-30-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 15:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-03-30-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>The Open IoT Developer Challenge is an annual challenge to promote the use of open source and open standards in IoT solutions. The winners were selected this month and they will be joining us to prese…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CeBIT 2016</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-03-14-cebit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-03-14-cebit/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EclipseCon - IoT Summit 2016</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-03-10-eclipsecon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-03-10-eclipsecon/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Kura: A gateway framework built for IoT</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-03-07-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 19:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-03-07-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Eclipse Kura: A gateway framework built for IoT</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Embedded World 2016</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-02-23-embedded-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-02-23-embedded-world/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Vorto as a Service</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-02-10-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 17:09:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-02-10-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>For the IoT domain cloud based solutions are getting more and more important. In this context buzzwords like SaaS, PaaS, or just microservices are common vocabularies. This trend of course also affect…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OGC SensorThings: IoT Data Interoperability with a GeoWeb approach</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-02-01-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 18:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-02-01-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>OGC SensorThings: IoT Data Interoperability with a GeoWeb approachstrial Automation &amp;amp; Industrial IoT</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Evolution Expo</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-01-26-iot-evolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2016-01-26-iot-evolution/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An IoT Software Suite to Connect Products to Customers’ Business</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/case-studies/connected-products-with-eclipse-kura/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/case-studies/connected-products-with-eclipse-kura/</guid>
      <description>Solair started in Italy in 2011 with the observation that enterprise software severely lagged behind consumer software in affordability and simplicity. They have worked with customers in many industries including smart cities, manufacturing, industrial machinery and retail. Solair has recently begun to expand to do business mainly in Japan, Germany and the United States.  “There are still many companies that don’t completely understand how to benefit from the potential advantages of connected products and they are looking for ready to use solutions that are quick to implement and bring measurable economic results,” said Martina Casani, Marketing Director, Solair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT case study: An IoT Software Suite to Connect Products to Customers’ Business</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-01-27-case-study-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-01-27-case-study-03/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Summit: An opportunity to learn what open source can offer to IoT</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-12-21-iot-summit-an-opportunity-to-learn-what-open-source-can-offer-iot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-12-21-iot-summit-an-opportunity-to-learn-what-open-source-can-offer-iot/</guid>
      <description>The Eclipse IoT community has grown significantly over the last 1-2 years. There are now 20+ Eclipse IoT projects building open source technology for IoT solutions. We are well on our way to providing the key building blocks developers need to build IoT solutions…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to OPC-UA: Interoperability for Industrial Automation &amp; Industrial IoT</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-01-14-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2016 16:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2016-01-14-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>OPC-UA is the interoperability standard for the secure and reliable exchange of data and information in the industrial automation space and in other industries. It is platform independent and ensures …</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Virtual Power Plants</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/case-studies/building-virtual-power-plants/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/case-studies/building-virtual-power-plants/</guid>
      <description>The Business Application – Monitoring Industrial Power Distribution  Kevin Read and his father, John Read, have a background in energy data monitoring and noticed a market need a few years ago. Large data centers worldwide are using rack-mountable power distribution units (PDUs) to control and monitor electrical power in the data center. These smart PDUs measure the power consumption of each device plugged into the socket, along with temperature, humidity and other environmental factors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT case study: Building Virtual Power Plants</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-12-22-case-study-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-12-22-case-study-02/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT case study: Monitoring Industrial Power Distribution</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-12-22-case-study-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-12-22-case-study-01/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT’s 2015 Year in Review</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-12-21-2015-year-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-12-21-2015-year-in-review/</guid>
      <description>Come the end of the year and you usually want to look back at what you’ve accomplished during the past twelve months.
For us, at Eclipse IoT, it’s been a pretty busy and successful year! So without further ado, here are the 5 most noteworthy things that happened in the Eclipse IoT community this year.…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring Industrial Power Distribution</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/case-studies/monitoring-industrial-power-distribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/case-studies/monitoring-industrial-power-distribution/</guid>
      <description>The business application: building virtual power plants  E.ON Connecting Energies is a business unit of E.ON and an international provider of integrated energy solutions for commercial and industrial customers as well as public- sector institutions. E.ON is an international privately- owned energy supplier and will in future be focusing entirely on renewables, energy networks and customer solutions. In the 2014 financial year, more than 58,000 employees based in many countries in Europe as well as in Russia and North America generated sales of around EUR 112 billion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Charging of Electric Vehicles with RISE V2G Project</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-12-16-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 16:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-12-16-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>RISE V2G is a Reference Implementation Supporting the Evolution of the Vehicle-2-Grid communication interface ISO 15118. The international standard ISO 15118, entitled &amp;ldquo;Road vehicles - Vehicle to grid…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IEEE World Forum on Internet of Things</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-12-16-ieee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-12-16-ieee/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing The 16 Winners Of The Open Iot Challenge Starter Kit!</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-12-09-open-iot-challenge-devkits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-12-09-open-iot-challenge-devkits/</guid>
      <description>It’s now been a bit more than 2 weeks since the second edition of the Open IoT Challenge has officially started. More than 80 teams have applied to be part of the challenge, and if you ask me, that’s really exciting!…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Arduino C&#43;&#43; IDE for Eclipse</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-12-02-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 16:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-12-02-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>The Arduino IDE from arduino.cc provides a simple IDE that lets these hobbyists get started. However, it is really simple. As projects get bigger and more complex, Arduino developers need something mo…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SPS IPC Drives 2015</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-11-23-sps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-11-23-sps/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A new name: Eclipse NeoSCADA</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-11-19-neoscada/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-11-19-neoscada/</guid>
      <description>In 2013 through the move to the Eclipse Foundation, the existing openSCADA project became Eclipse SCADA. Being a very industrial oriented project it naturally has a different audience than most other projects…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SensorUp</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/sensorup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/sensorup/</guid>
      <description>Data from all your different sensors, accessible in a single platform
SensorUp makes information from all different kinds of sensors accessible in a single platform, by using open standards to connect the sensors. Our IoT Platform is the world&amp;rsquo;s first, most complete, compliant implementation of the OGC SensorThings API.
SensorThings API was purpose-built for IoT, and manages low power, low bandwidth, and intermittent connectivity situations. The standard isREST-based and JSON encoded,so it&amp;rsquo;s developer friendly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Things Network: an open &amp; free IoT network for the masses</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-11-12-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2015 17:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-11-12-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Join us on next Thursday to learn more about The Things Network with Johan Stokking.
Last June, my co-founder Wienke heard about a piece of hardware that would create coverage for Internet of Things …</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open IoT Challenge - Second edition!</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-11-09-open-iot-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-11-09-open-iot-challenge/</guid>
      <description>We are happy to unveil the second edition of the Open IoT Challenge. Submit your application before November 23 to get a chance to win one of our numerous prizes and hardware kits!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EclipseCon Europe 2015</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-11-03-eclipsecon-europe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-11-03-eclipsecon-europe/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Your IoT Services &amp; Applications with COMPOSE Platform</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-10-29-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 16:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-10-29-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>COMPOSE platform enables new services that can integrate the Internet of Services with the Internet of Things. Connected devices are associated to services that can be combined and managed in a standa…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaOne 2015</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-10-25-javaone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-10-25-javaone/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT at JavaOne 2015</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-10-25-eclipse-iot-at-javaone-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-10-25-eclipse-iot-at-javaone-2015/</guid>
      <description>If you are attending JavaOne this week, I want to make sure you don’t miss out on the many opportunities to learn more about Eclipse IoT, and meet the people behind it. You can find us at the Eclipse Foundation booth (#5710). There will be…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial: Connecting Eclipse Kura to AWS IoT</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-10-23-kura-and-aws-iot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-10-23-kura-and-aws-iot/</guid>
      <description>Just a few weeks ago, Amazon Web Services (AWS) announced that they added the ability for their customers to manage IoT solutions. More specifically, they are offering a managed IoT platform that allows to connect your devices using HTTP or MQTT, and that integrates with other AWS services…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coding Serbia Conference</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-10-08-codingserbia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-10-08-codingserbia/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MangOH</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/hardware/mangoh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/hardware/mangoh/</guid>
      <description>Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ReliaGATE 10-20</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/hardware/reliagate-10-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/hardware/reliagate-10-20/</guid>
      <description>Lorem ipsum Occaecat ex reprehenderit sint aliqua magna reprehenderit pariatur in incididunt ut qui reprehenderit magna et exercitation ex reprehenderit adipisicing occaecat Duis irure ex reprehenderit aute occaecat commodo commodo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT is Everywhere at EclipseCon Europe</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-10-01-iot-is-everywhere-ateclipsecon-europe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-10-01-iot-is-everywhere-ateclipsecon-europe/</guid>
      <description>The best thing about the Eclipse IoT community is that participants are real IoT practitioners and IoT experts. Our face-2-face meetings bring together senior technical leaders that are working on the core technology…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siemens</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/siemens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/siemens/</guid>
      <description>Siemens is a global powerhouse in electrical engineering and electronics. The company has 343,000 employees (as of September 30, 2014) working to develop and manufacture products, design and install complex systems and projects, and tailor a wide range of services for individual requirements.
Electrification, automation and digitalization are the long-term growth fields of Siemens. In order to take full advantage of the market potential in these fields, our businesses are bundled into nine divisions and healthcare as a separately managed business: Power and Gas, Wind Power and Renewables, Power Generation Services, Energy Management, Building Technologies, Mobility, Digital Factory, Process Industries and Drives, Financial Services, and Healthcare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Zulu Embedded and running Java on Intel® Edison and Galileo</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-09-24-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 16:49:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-09-24-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Zulu Embedded is fully certified, 100% open source Java SE platform based on OpenJDK for embedded devices, M2M, and IoT. Java’s growth in the embedded and IoT space has been limited by licensing and …</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industry of Things World</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-09-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-09-21/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Eclipse IoT Demo Box</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-09-16-unveiling-the-eclipse-iot-demo-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-09-16-unveiling-the-eclipse-iot-demo-box/</guid>
      <description>Now that the holiday season is over, we’re fully into “conference season” mode, as the fall is packed with IoT conferences (look at our Events Calendar to see where we will have a presence in the next couple months). Last week, the Eclipse Foundation was exhibiting at M2M Summit…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building &amp; managing IoT applications with LightweightM2M</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-09-10-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 16:04:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-09-10-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>In this webinar we will present how to solve those problems using OMA LightweightM2M and Eclipse IoT projects Leshan and Wakaama.
We will cover the following topics:
 From M2M to Web-of-things, new…  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M2M Summit 2015</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-09-08-m2m-summit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-09-08-m2m-summit/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 hardware platforms of choice to get started with Eclipse IoT</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-09-16-three-hardware-platforms-of-choice-to-get-started-with-eclipse-iot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-09-16-three-hardware-platforms-of-choice-to-get-started-with-eclipse-iot/</guid>
      <description>When you prototype IoT solutions, it becomes necessary very early in your development phase to use an actual embedded platform to run your software, and to test it in an environment that is as close as possible of what you expect your production environment to be…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MQTT Security Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-08-10-mqtt-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-08-10-mqtt-security/</guid>
      <description>Following their MQTT Essentials series, the HiveMQ team is back with 10 great articles on how to secure data exchanges when implementing MQTT communication scenarios. A must read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remote management of an mbed device with LwM2M, Wakaama &amp; Leshan</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-08-10-lwm2m-leshan-wakaama-mbed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-08-10-lwm2m-leshan-wakaama-mbed/</guid>
      <description>In this video, you can see how Eclipse Wakaama (C implementation of LwM2M) has been ported to an mbed NXP LPC1768 – a device with just 32KB of RAM! – and is controlled from Eclipse Leshan, a LwM2M server in Java.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growing an open community: 3 interesting facts about Eclipse IoT</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-08-07-growing-an-iot-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-08-07-growing-an-iot-community/</guid>
      <description>About 9 months ago, I published a blog post showing up some interesting metrics about the Eclipse IoT open-source community. I have recently crunched the numbers again and here are 3 interesting facts about Eclipse IoT and its developer community…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT? No more excuses. Solair to launch “IoT-in-a-Box”</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-07-31-solair-iot-in-a-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-07-31-solair-iot-in-a-box/</guid>
      <description>Solair Corporate announces the first IoT “off-the-shelf” product that allows you to connect machines, things and sensors in a few clicks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programming IoT Gateways in JavaScript with macchina.io</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-07-23-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 16:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-07-23-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>In this talk +Günter Obiltschnig will introduce macchina.io (http://macchina.io), a new open source platform for programming Linux-based IoT gateway devices. macchina.io provides a rich programming en…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CA Technologies</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/ca/</guid>
      <description>CA Technologies (NASDAQ: CA) creates software that fuels transformation for companies and enables them to seize the opportunities of the application economy. Software is at the heart of every business, in every industry. From planning to development to management and security, CA is working with companies worldwide to change the way we live, transact and communicate.
CA software and solutions help our customers drive enterprise-wide productivity, offer differentiated user experiences and open new growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn from IoT experts with the Virtual IoT meetup group</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-07-14-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-07-14-meetup/</guid>
      <description>About a year ago, we realized that although the IoT is on everyone’s lips, there is a huge lack of technical resources available for people interested in learning more and getting their hands dirty with…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with MQTT: Everything you need to know about the lightweight IoT protocol</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-07-02-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2015 16:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-07-02-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Our digital world is growing rapidly and we have more devices connected to the internet than ever. On top of that every second 80 new devices are added, which introduces new challenges to communicatio…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with MQTT</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-07-02-virtualiot-mqtt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2015 17:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-07-02-virtualiot-mqtt/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generative Software</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/generative-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/generative-software/</guid>
      <description>Generative Software is an Eclipse Solution Member since 2011 and joined the Working Group in summer 2015. It aims to provide DSLs, a canonical IoT meta model and Open-Source code generators that target the Eclipse IoT components and projects. This allows you to design and develop complete IoT solutions in a model-driven way, do rapid prototyping and keep track of the solution’s system and software architecture. At the same time, the Virtual Developer Platform serves as a central place, where many different IoT related generators can be found and all of them are accessed in a uniform way, without installation on a developer’s computer, no matter who develops or owns a generator (device manufacturer, platform vendor, solution developer, …).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MQTT Essentials</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-07-01-mqtt-essentials/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-07-01-mqtt-essentials/</guid>
      <description>Eclipse IoT Working Group member dc-square, who develops the HiveMQ MQTT broker, has put together a great series of articles to help you master MQTT. Check it out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EclipseCon France 2015</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-06-24-eclipseconfrance2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-06-24-eclipseconfrance2015/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huawei</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/huawei/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/huawei/</guid>
      <description>Huawei Technologies is a high-tech enterprise which specializes in research and development (R&amp;amp;D), production and marketing of communications equipment, providing customized network solutions for telecom carriers in optical, fixed, mobile and data communications networks.
Huawei’s IoT platform is open and standard based. It provides a common foundation across different applications and services. Its flexible and scalable architecture supports both Carrier and Enterprise market. The unified authentication and flexible data management Improves MSISDN Resource Utilization and provides Anti-theft, anti-attack and anti-embezzlement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O&#39;Reilly SOLID</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-06-23-solidcon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2015 16:12:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-06-23-solidcon/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Security: An open source and open standard approach</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-06-15-iot-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-06-15-iot-security/</guid>
      <description>High on any list of IoT concerns is the security for an IoT solution. How do you make sure devices only talk to the correct servers and only the ‘correct’ devices talk to your servers? Lots of people…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bridging IoTivity and Eclipse SmartHome</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-06-12-iotivity-and-smarthome/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-06-12-iotivity-and-smarthome/</guid>
      <description>There are several ongoing initiatives that aim at standardizing protocols and interfaces in order to enable a truly interoperable Internet of Things. On the protocol front, I would certainly argue…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working without wires: Simulating hardware components for IoT application development</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-06-10-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 16:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-06-10-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>IoT software development is often slowed or delayed because the target hardware is unfinished, unstable, or just a few units are available. Existing hardware simulation tools allow developers to test …</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simulating hardware components for IoT application development</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-06-10-kinoma/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-06-10-kinoma/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ESP8266 programming from Eclipse</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-06-08-esp8266-eclipse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-06-08-esp8266-eclipse/</guid>
      <description>A really nice article on how to setup Eclipse to program the ESP8266, an incredibly cheap ($3!) and versatile IoT WiFi chip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical Operational Intelligence and Fast Time to Value for the IoT</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-05-27-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 16:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-05-27-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>There’s no good reason for Operational Intelligence or data-driven insights to be a bottleneck for progress or innovation, especially when it comes to the Internet of Things (IoT). Learn how Splunk’s …</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical Operational Intelligence and Fast Time to Value for the IoT</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-05-27-virtualiot-splunk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-05-27-virtualiot-splunk/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse IoT Breakfast</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-05-12-iot-breakfast-madrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-05-12-iot-breakfast-madrid/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internet of Things: The Role of Free and Open Source Software</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-05-20-webinar-dla-piper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-05-20-webinar-dla-piper/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating end-to-end IoT applications with Eclipse Kura &amp; Solair IoT Platform</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-05-14-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 15:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-05-14-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>SLIDES: http://www.slideshare.net/solaircorporate/creating-endtoend-iot-applications-with-eclipse-kura-solair-iot-platform
Starting from the winner project of the first Eclipse Open IoT Challenge, Ca…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating end-to-end IoT applications with Eclipse Kura &amp; Solair IoT Platform</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-05-14-virtualiot-solair/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-05-14-virtualiot-solair/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT World</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-05-12-iot-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 16:12:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-05-12-iot-world/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azul Systems Joins Eclipse Foundation</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-05-12-azul/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-05-12-azul/</guid>
      <description>Azul Systems (Azul), the award-winning leader in Java runtime solutions, today announced its membership in the Eclipse Foundation, bringing over a decade of Java knowledge and expertise to multiple…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The IoT Gateway Dream Team: Eclipse Kura &amp; Apache Camel</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-05-06-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 15:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-05-06-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Slides from the presentation available at: http://www.slideshare.net/hekonsek/io-t-gateway-dream-team-eclipse-kura-and-apache-camel
Eclipse Kura is the well recognized field gateway for Internet Of T…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT DevCon</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-05-06-iot-devcon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-05-06-iot-devcon/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The IoT Gateway Dream Team: Eclipse Kura &amp; Apache Camel</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-05-06-virtualiot-kura-camel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-05-06-virtualiot-kura-camel/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azul Systems</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/azul/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/azul/</guid>
      <description>Azul Systems is the world’s only company that is 100% focused on Java and Java runtime technology. We believe that we can help the IoT developers take advantage of the power and productivity of Java by reducing the frictions (licensing costs, field-of-use restrictions) and perceptions (footprint, etc.) gating widespread adoption of the language throughout the IoT.
As members of the Eclipse community we are bringing Zulu and Zulu Embedded – our 100% open source JDKs, to the IoT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Hat, Inc.</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/redhat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/redhat/</guid>
      <description>Red Hat, the world&amp;rsquo;s leading open source solutions provider, is headquartered in Raleigh, NC with over 50 satellite offices spanning the globe. CIOs have ranked Red Hat first for value in Enterprise Software for four consecutive years in the CIO Insight Magazine Vendor Value study.Red Hat provides high-quality, affordable technology with its operating system platform, Red Hat Enterprise Linux, together with applications, management and Services Oriented Architecture (SOA) solutions, including the JBoss Enterprise Middleware Suite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview with Benjamin Cabé on the Internet of Things at Eclipse</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-04-15-infoq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-04-15-infoq/</guid>
      <description>Recorded at EclipseCon 2015</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journée IoT INSA</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-04-09-iot-insa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-04-09-iot-insa/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Open IoT Challenge Winners</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-04-08-iot-challenge-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-04-08-iot-challenge-results/</guid>
      <description>Oh boy, this has been a difficult call, but we are happy to finally be able to announce the three winners of our Open IoT Challenge! The challenge has been keeping our participants busy for two months, and…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Developer Survey: What are developers doing with IoT?</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-04-03-survey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-04-03-survey/</guid>
      <description>We have just published the results of the first IoT Developer Survey. There are some very interesting findings so I encourage you to check out the report. The raw data is also available…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse OM2M Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-03-29-om2m-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-03-29-om2m-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>If you want to develop plug-ins for the Eclipse OM2M project, an implementation of the SmartM2M standard, this is the perfect tutorial to get you started!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open IoT Challenge – Final submissions</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-03-26-open-iot-final-entries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-03-26-open-iot-final-entries/</guid>
      <description>The Open IoT challenge ended earlier this week, and it was pretty exciting to see the final submissions coming in the form of blog posts and video during the last hours before the deadline…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open IoT Stack for Java Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-03-24-java-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2015-03-24-java-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>Using Eclipse Kura, MQTT and CoAP to build a smart greenhouse. Java is almost 20 years old, and has over the years gathered a very large community of developers that in turn fostered an even larger ecosystem of open-source components and frameworks.
Thanks to the recent efforts towards making Java…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Conference – Spring</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-03-23-iot-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 16:12:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-03-23-iot-conference/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Open IoT Challenge projects are way cool</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-03-19-the-open-iot-challenge-project-are-way-cool/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-03-19-the-open-iot-challenge-project-are-way-cool/</guid>
      <description>There are only a few days left for the participants to the Open IoT Challenge to wrap up their projects and share the final results of what they have achieved over the course of the last couple months…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Day Dresden</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-03-18-eclipse-day-dresden/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-03-18-eclipse-day-dresden/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EclipseCon NA 2015</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-03-09-eclipsecon2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/events/2015-03-09-eclipsecon2015/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sierra Wireless</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/sierra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/sierra/</guid>
      <description>Sierra Wireless is the global leader in machine-to-machine (M2M) devices and cloud services, delivering intelligent wireless solutions that simplify the connected world. We offer the industry&amp;rsquo;s most comprehensive portfolio of 2G, 3G and 4G embedded modules and gateways, seamlessly integrated with our secure M2M cloud services.
Sierra Wireless is deeply involved in the Eclipse IoT community: we founded the IoT Working Group, and are contributing to several projects including Wakaama, Californium, LDT,… The Eclipse IoT technologies are also used in our AirVantage M2M Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>openHAB Foundation</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/openhab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/openhab/</guid>
      <description>The openHAB Foundation e.V. is a non-profit organisation.
Its purpose is to educate the public about the possibilities that Free software offers in the domain of smart homes.
More and more new technologies and devices are introduced to our living, working and business environment. Although all of them are designed to make our lives easier, they have a common problem: The lack of interoperability, due to incompatible technology stacks and conflicting commercial interests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Litmus Automation</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/litmus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/litmus/</guid>
      <description>Litmus Automation aims to help businesses adapt to the smart revolution in technology by enabling connected solutions. The company&amp;rsquo;s full-featured Internet of Things platform Loop aids in accelerating revenue generation and operational business impact from connected applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M2M Alliance</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/m2m-alliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/m2m-alliance/</guid>
      <description>As the largest association for the machine-to-machine sector, the M2M Alliance is considered the platform and voice for providers and users of M2M solutions. The primary objective of the M2M Alliance is to promote M2M technologies and solutions. The M2M Alliance actively advocates for the economic interests of its members, and promotes cooperation and the exchange of experiences among the various sectors and companies. The M2M Alliance represents the interests of the M2M industry by creating better general conditions for attractive and lucrative M2M solutions through the constant interaction among industry, R&amp;amp;D and policy makers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LAAS-CNRS</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/laas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/laas/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>itemis</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/itemis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/itemis/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GadgetKeeper</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/gadgetkeeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/gadgetkeeper/</guid>
      <description>GadgetKeeper is an Internet Of Things platform allowing the rapid creation if IoT solutions to connect your sensors, devices, equipment (&amp;ldquo;Things&amp;rdquo;) with people and systems.
GadgetKeeper&amp;rsquo;s technology eliminates complexity by simplifying and standardizing the way information is managed and exchanged so that physical and virtual assets and services can work together as one integrated system.
GadgetKeeper provides you with foundational IoT building blocks (compete object model for things/services, templates and versioning, reach data types, programmable business logic) and services (data storage, time series, multiple communication protocols, integration with external services, life-cycle management and elastic scalability) allowing you to focus on product innovation rather than on enabling infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBH SYSTEMS</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/ibh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/ibh/</guid>
      <description>IBH SYSTEMS GmbH is the lead developer of the Eclipse SCADA system, a true open source SCADA platform.
Eclipse SCADA offers a fully featured SCADA platform from the integration of field devices, over middleware functionality, to HMI components. It provides a communication abstraction layer, monitoring and archival services, a visual interface and a sophisticated system to configure complex SCADA installations. As the lead developer, IBH SYSTEMS GmbH offers consulting, custom development and integration for Eclipse SCADA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/ibm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/ibm/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MicroEJ</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/microej/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/microej/</guid>
      <description>MicroEJ is an independent software vendor of cost-driven solutions for the smart digital world. With more than $20M of R&amp;amp;D investment, MicroEJ is focused on providing turnkey software products to solve the embedded worlds major business challenges and to enable application-driven uses and services in the IoT world commensurate with the cost and resource constraints of that world. MicroEJ helps OEMs create flexible and future-proof smart devices, brings rich user experiences, and enables additional sources of revenue across the whole value chain, from sensor data collection to cloud-based services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deutsche Telekom</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/dtag/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/dtag/</guid>
      <description>QIVICON is an alliance of leading German industrial companies, initiated by Deutsche Telekom AG with the aim of promoting the field of Smart Home technology and providing solutions for customers on a multi-manufacturer basis. Together with its partners EnBW, eQ-3, Miele and Samsung, Deutsche Telekom is developing a platform that covers areas such as energy efficiency, security and convenience in the home for people of every age group. QIVICON enables appliances and functions from different brands to be combined easily in the Smart Home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eurotech</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/eurotech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/eurotech/</guid>
      <description>Eurotech believes in open, standards-based systems to deliver on the promise of the Internet of Things, and works with world-class partners and organizations to evangelize that strategy, including as a founding member of the IoT Working Group in the Eclipse Foundation and OASIS MQTT Technical Committee. Eurotech has contributed the Kura project to the Eclipse Foundation and actively participates in many associated projects and activities.
Eurotech solutions combine software, application framework, hardware, and device cloud services that drive business success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canonical</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/canonical/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/canonical/</guid>
      <description>Canonical is the company behind Ubuntu, the leading Operating System for cloud and Internet of Things. Most public cloud workloads are running on Ubuntu, as do smart gateways, self-driving cars and advanced robots. Canonical has been a proponent of open source since 2004, committed to creating it, refining it, certifying it for reliability and promoting its use.
Canonical leads the development of the snap universal Linux packaging system for secure, transactional device updates and app stores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dc-square</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/dcsquare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/dcsquare/</guid>
      <description>dc-square is a company based in Southern Germany building software solutions for the Internet of Things. Our product HiveMQ is a MQTT broker for the enterprise, which makes it possible to connect thousands and millions of devices over wired or wireless networks with very efficient bandwidth usage and push technology. Our focus is on providing IoT building blocks for the enterprise and advice on, consult on or implement IoT solutions for companies around them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitreactive</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/bitreactive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/bitreactive/</guid>
      <description>Bitreactive makes Reactive Blocks, a tool designed to accelerate and simplify M2M and IoT software development. Its benefits are especially well suited for applications that run autonomously on gateways. Functionality that is often used is provided by dedicated building blocks, for instance for protocols like MQTT or Modbus, access to data collection APIs or processing and buffering of data. The tool checks if applications work correctly with regard to their behavior, and detects a range of errors automatically that are hard to find by traditional testing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bosch Software Innovations</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/bosch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/bosch/</guid>
      <description>Bosch Software Innovations GmbH, the Bosch Group&amp;rsquo;s software and systems house, designs, develops, and operates innovative software and system solutions that help our customers around the world both in the Internet of Things and in the traditional enterprise environment. We place particular focus on the topics of mobility, energy, manufacturing, and smart home.
The focus of the Eclipse Vorto project, which has been proposed by Bosch Software Innovations, is the standardization of so called information models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenText Analytics</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/opentext/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/opentext/</guid>
      <description>OpenText Analytics and Reporting products make data-driven applications simple for everyone in your organization, including developers, employees, partners, IT, and customers. Build enterprise reporting applications that are as unique as your business, personalized to meet your data needs in any industry, on any platform, for any device.
To stay competitive, your organization needs to make the right business decisions at the right time, with compelling data to back up your actions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Case Study MQTT: Why Open Source and Open Standards Drives Adoption</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-03-04-case-study-mqtt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-03-04-case-study-mqtt/</guid>
      <description>For the last 3 years, we have been talking about why IoT needs open source and open standards to be successful. We are now seeing great examples of why this is so true and why open communities will lead IoT adoption…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Open IoT Challenge</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-02-09-announcing-open-iot-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 16:28:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/news/2015-02-09-announcing-open-iot-challenge/</guid>
      <description>2014 is almost over, and one of the first big events for Eclipse IoT next year will be EclipseCon 2015, March 9-12 in Burlingame, California. If you haven’t seen the EclipseCon program already, I highly…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bring Your IoT Ideas to Life with the WunderBar</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2014-12-16-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 16:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2014-12-16-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>You’re full of fantastic IoT ideas, but bringing them to fruition is never an easy task. Especially when it comes time to work with your sensors and electronics. Hardware can present a significant obs…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building home gateways with Eclipse SmartHome</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2014-11-04-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 16:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2014-11-04-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Slides are available on Slideshare: http://slideshare.net/xthirtynine/eclipse-smart-home-webinar
Despite the buzz around the Internet of Things (IoT) there are still many devices, systems and protoco…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing an open plaform for your SCADA project</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2014-10-21-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2014 15:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2014-10-21-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Eclipse SCADA provides a platform independent, comprehensive SCADA solution from the connection to the field devices, through the data enrichment in the SCADA server, and the visualization for the use…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OM2M: Standardized service platform for M2M interoperability</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2014-10-14-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2014 15:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2014-10-14-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Machine-to Machine (M2M) promises to interconnect billions of devices in near future covering various domains. However, M2M is suffering from a high vertical fragmentation of current M2M markets and l…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualize IoT data with BIRT</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2014-10-07-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2014 15:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2014-10-07-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>IoT refers to the connection and intercommunication of different devices, systems, and services in a single platform. This plays right into BIRT&amp;rsquo;s ability to connect to and relate many different sourc…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting Sensor Networks</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2014-09-23-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2014 15:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2014-09-23-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Slides: http://www.slideshare.net/mkovatsc/virtual-iot-meetup-connecting-sensor-networks Sensor networks are a fundamental building of Internet of Things (IoT) applications, as they provide the interf…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building the Internet of Things with the Eclipse IoT stack: a practical example</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2014-09-16-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2014 15:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2014-09-16-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>It may seem hard to get started with the Internet of Things (IoT) with so many technologies, protocols, hardware platforms, … involved. In this session, Benjamin Cabé from the Eclipse Foundation will …</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Gateway: Reducing the distance between embedded and enterprise technologies</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2014-09-09-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2014 15:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/resources/2014-09-09-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>Slides of the presentation: http://slideshare.net/Eurotechchannel/kuram2miotgateway
Internet of Things adoption is constrained by disparate implementations and proprietary solutions. The emergence of…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/cloud/dummy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/cloud/dummy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/gateways/dummy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/gateways/dummy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/dummy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/open-iot-challenge/dummy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/projects/dummy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/projects/dummy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/working-group/dummy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/working-group/dummy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>