<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>The Open IoT Challenge projects are way cool</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2015-03-19-the-open-iot-challenge-project-are-way-cool/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2015-03-19-the-open-iot-challenge-project-are-way-cool/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are only a few days left for the participants to the Open IoT Challenge to wrap up their projects and share the final results of what they have achieved over the course of the last couple months…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Day Dresden</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/eclipse-day-dresden/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/eclipse-day-dresden/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EclipseCon NA 2015</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/eclipsecon2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/eclipsecon2015/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sierra Wireless</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/member/sierra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/member/sierra/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sierra Wireless is the global leader in machine-to-machine (M2M) devices and cloud services, delivering intelligent wireless solutions that simplify the connected world. We offer the industry&amp;rsquo;s most comprehensive portfolio of 2G, 3G and 4G embedded modules and gateways, seamlessly integrated with our secure M2M cloud services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sierra Wireless is deeply involved in the Eclipse IoT community: we founded the IoT Working Group, and are contributing to several projects including Wakaama, Californium, LDT,… The Eclipse IoT technologies are also used in our AirVantage M2M Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>openHAB UG</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/member/openhab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/member/openhab/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;openHAB UG (haftungsbeschränkt) is the company behind the open-source home automation solution openHAB and believes that an open-source stack is the only right answer for home gateways. openHAB UG therefore initiated the Eclipse SmartHome project and is the lead developer behind it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Eclipse SmartHome project is a framework that allows building smart home solutions that have a strong focus on heterogeneous environments, i.e. solutions that deal with the integration of different protocols or standards. Its purpose is to provide a uniform access to devices and information and to facilitate different kinds of interactions with them.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Litmus Automation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/member/litmus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/member/litmus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M2M Alliance</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/member/m2m-alliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/member/m2m-alliance/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>itemis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/member/itemis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/member/itemis/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LAAS-CNRS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/member/laas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/member/laas/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GadgetKeeper</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/member/gadgetkeeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/member/gadgetkeeper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GadgetKeeper is an Internet Of Things platform allowing the rapid creation if IoT solutions to connect your sensors, devices, equipment (&amp;ldquo;Things&amp;rdquo;) with people and systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GadgetKeeper&amp;rsquo;s technology eliminates complexity by simplifying and standardizing the way information is managed and exchanged so that physical and virtual assets and services can work together as one integrated system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GadgetKeeper provides you with foundational IoT building blocks (compete object model for things/services, templates and versioning, reach data types, programmable business logic) and services (data storage, time series, multiple communication protocols, integration with external services, life-cycle management and elastic scalability) allowing you to focus on product innovation rather than on enabling infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBH SYSTEMS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/member/ibh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/member/ibh/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;IBH SYSTEMS GmbH is the lead developer of the Eclipse SCADA system, a true open source SCADA platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eclipse SCADA offers a fully featured SCADA platform from the integration of field devices, over middleware functionality, to HMI components. It provides a communication abstraction layer, monitoring and archival services, a visual interface and a sophisticated system to configure complex SCADA installations. As the lead developer, IBH SYSTEMS GmbH offers consulting, custom development and integration for Eclipse SCADA.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/member/ibm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/member/ibm/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deutsche Telekom</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/member/dtag/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/member/dtag/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eurotech</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/member/eurotech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/member/eurotech/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Eurotech believes in open, standards-based systems to deliver on the promise of the Internet of Things, and works with world-class partners and organizations to evangelize that strategy, including as a founding member of the IoT Working Group in the Eclipse Foundation and OASIS MQTT Technical Committee. Eurotech has contributed the Kura project to the Eclipse Foundation and actively participates in many associated projects and activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eurotech solutions combine software, application framework, hardware, and device cloud services that drive business success. A global leader in connecting distributed devices that make up the Internet of Things, Eurotech collaborates with progressive customers, partners, and integrators to bring rugged, reliable and cost effective device and data management solutions to market. Combining technology excellence with domain expertise allows Eurotech to meet the needs of key market segments including healthcare, security, transportation, energy, and industrial.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canonical</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/member/canonical/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/member/canonical/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>