<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eclipse IoT</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eclipse IoT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/working-group/dummy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/working-group/dummy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Gateway: Reducing the distance between embedded and enterprise technologies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/2014-09-09-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2014 15:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resources/2014-09-09-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Slides of the presentation: &lt;a href=&#34;http://slideshare.net/Eurotechchannel/kuram2miotgateway&#34;&gt;http://slideshare.net/Eurotechchannel/kuram2miotgateway&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Internet of Things adoption is constrained by disparate implementations and proprietary solutions. The emergence of…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building the Internet of Things with the Eclipse IoT stack: a practical example</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/2014-09-16-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2014 15:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resources/2014-09-16-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It may seem hard to get started with the Internet of Things (IoT) with so many technologies, protocols, hardware platforms, … involved. In this session, Benjamin Cabé from the Eclipse Foundation will …&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting Sensor Networks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/2014-09-23-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2014 15:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resources/2014-09-23-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Slides: &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.slideshare.net/mkovatsc/virtual-iot-meetup-connecting-sensor-networks&#34;&gt;http://www.slideshare.net/mkovatsc/virtual-iot-meetup-connecting-sensor-networks&lt;/a&gt;
Sensor networks are a fundamental building of Internet of Things (IoT) applications, as they provide the interf…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualize IoT data with BIRT</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/2014-10-07-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2014 15:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resources/2014-10-07-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;IoT refers to the connection and intercommunication of different devices, systems, and services in a single platform. This plays right into BIRT&amp;rsquo;s ability to connect to and relate many different sourc…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OM2M: Standardized service platform for M2M interoperability</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/2014-10-14-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2014 15:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resources/2014-10-14-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Machine-to Machine (M2M) promises to interconnect billions of devices in near future covering various domains. However, M2M is suffering from a high vertical fragmentation of current M2M markets and l…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing an open plaform for your SCADA project</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/2014-10-21-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2014 15:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resources/2014-10-21-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Eclipse SCADA provides a platform independent, comprehensive SCADA solution from the connection to the field devices, through the data enrichment in the SCADA server, and the visualization for the use…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building home gateways with Eclipse SmartHome</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/2014-11-04-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 16:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resources/2014-11-04-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Slides are available on Slideshare: &lt;a href=&#34;http://slideshare.net/xthirtynine/eclipse-smart-home-webinar&#34;&gt;http://slideshare.net/xthirtynine/eclipse-smart-home-webinar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the buzz around the Internet of Things (IoT) there are still many devices, systems and protoco…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bring Your IoT Ideas to Life with the WunderBar</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/2014-12-16-virtual-iot-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 16:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resources/2014-12-16-virtual-iot-recording/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You’re full of fantastic IoT ideas, but bringing them to fruition is never an easy task. Especially when it comes time to work with your sensors and electronics. Hardware can present a significant obs…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Open IoT Challenge</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2015-02-09-announcing-open-iot-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 16:28:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2015-02-09-announcing-open-iot-challenge/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;2014 is almost over, and one of the first big events for Eclipse IoT next year will be EclipseCon 2015, March 9-12 in Burlingame, California.
If you haven’t seen the EclipseCon program already, I highly…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Case Study MQTT: Why Open Source and Open Standards Drives Adoption</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2015-03-04-case-study-mqtt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2015-03-04-case-study-mqtt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For the last 3 years, we have been talking about why IoT needs open source and open standards to be successful. We are now seeing great examples of why this is so true and why open communities will lead IoT adoption…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2lemetry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/member/2lemetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/member/2lemetry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;2lemetry is an IoT platform and solutions company that powers the connected enterprise, tying people, processes, data and devices together—transforming raw data into real-time actionable intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2lemetry&amp;rsquo;s ThingFabric platform acts as an IoT version of Enterprise Application Integration (EAI) middleware solutions, providing device connectivity at scale, cross-communication, data brokering and storage. We also help companies make sense of the captured data by offering actionable data intelligence through predictive computational models and a configurable rules engine.
The ThingFabric platform has a unique protocol-agnostic architecture that enables native support of multiple protocols (like MQTT, CoAP, STOMP, and M3DA), even allowing the customer to upload their own homegrown, proprietary or legacy protocols.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2lemetry actively contributes to the Paho project around objective-c and MQTT.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Actuate</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/member/actuate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/member/actuate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In 2004, Actuate co-founded &amp;ndash; and continues as its sole sponsor – the top-level Eclipse BIRT Project – an open source, Java-based IDE. BIRT is used as a workbench by more than 3.5 million developers around the globe, to reduce development time and significantly improve the efficacy of their customer-facing applications. BIRT has been downloaded over 13 million times since its inception. Please visit developer.actuate.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the commercial side, Actuate provides BIRT Designer Pro™ and BIRT iHub™ deployment software – to developers and IT departments of mid-size to global-brand enterprises, as well as to ISVs/OEMs. These organizations use BIRT to build scalable, secure solutions that provide valuable insights from data, and improve brand loyalty. These customers have delivered personalized analytics and insights to more than 200 million of their own customers, partners and employees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actuate also offers BIRT Analytics™ self-service, predictive analytics software for business analysts and marketers to enhance customer engagement using Big Data. The Actuate Customer Communications Suite™ empowers organizations to easily transform, process, personalize, archive and deliver high volume content and individualized correspondence. The Actuate PDF Accessibility Appliance™ is used to convert PDFs into documents that vision-impaired customers can “read.” Actuate is headquartered in Silicon Valley with more than 5,000 enterprise customers in financial services, technology and government.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitreactive</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/member/bitreactive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/member/bitreactive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bitreactive makes Reactive Blocks, a tool designed to accelerate and simplify M2M and IoT software development. Its benefits are especially well suited for applications that run autonomously on gateways. Functionality that is often used is provided by dedicated building blocks, for instance for protocols like MQTT or Modbus, access to data collection APIs or processing and buffering of data. The tool checks if applications work correctly with regard to their behavior, and detects a range of errors automatically that are hard to find by traditional testing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bosch Software Innovations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/member/bosch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/member/bosch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bosch Software Innovations GmbH, the Bosch Group&amp;rsquo;s software and systems house, designs, develops, and operates innovative software and system solutions that help our customers around the world both in the Internet of Things and in the traditional enterprise environment. We place particular focus on the topics of mobility, energy, manufacturing, and smart home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The focus of the Eclipse Vorto project, which has been proposed by Bosch Software Innovations, is the standardization of so called information models. These information models are abstract descriptions of real world devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition Bosch Software innovations is a member of the IoT Working Group and is a contributor to various open source projects (e.g. Californium, Wakaama) in the IoT context.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>