<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Member-rsses on Eclipse IoT</title>
    <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Member-rsses on Eclipse IoT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 15:31:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://iot.eclipse.org/member/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>CEA List</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/cealist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/cealist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;List, expert on digital systems&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based in Saclay (Paris region, France), List is a public research institute specialized in digital systems design. Its main mission is based on achieving excellence technological development on behalf of industrial partners for value creation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;100 industrial collaborations per year&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;List institute counts more than 700 partners and every year more than a 100 partnership activities are being conducted with French and foreign industrial companies on applied research projects in four main topics:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced Manufacturing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Embedded systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ambient intelligence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health ionizing radiations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
Labeled as Carnot Institute , List invests every year 25% of its budget into scientific resourcing actions in order to identify better tomorrows technological breakthroughs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CEA Tech as CEA (Commissariat a l&amp;rsquo;energie atomique et aux energies alternatives) Technological Research Division, gathers three specialised technological research institutes among which List institute specialised on digital systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;At a world class state-of-the-art&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our activity is based on three main pillars
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scientific excellence: List research engineers dedicate a 100% of their time to R&amp;amp;D activities and publish their results into international leading conferences and scientific journals. Keeping a strong link with academic research, they base their research on world-wide state of the art.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Culture of Industry:Our research teams are enlightened and motivated by a results-driven culture of projects, fixing themselves clear objectives to reach within committed deadlines and budgets. Each project launched by List Institute is fully assigned to permanent and suited human resources. The project management is based on a precise calendar, identified milestones and a clear description of deliverables. Research results confidentiality and intellectual property (patents) are defined by the parties in the collaboration agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opening to the world: List Institute is fully integrated into a local and national particularly dynamic ecosystem through strategic academic, institutional and industrial partnerships. In order to maintain the best level internationally in its fields of activity List institute is also involved in more than 200 European collaborative projects, collaborates with leading foreign academic laboratories and conducts research activities at an international level, especially in the USA.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung ARTIK</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/samsung/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/samsung/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Samsung and Eclipse&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an effort to strengthen our commitment to open source development, Samsung Semiconductor Inc. is proud to be a solution member of the Eclipse Foundation. In May 2015, Samsung announced the Samsung ARTIK Smart IoT platform in effort to provide an end-to-end solution to help accelerate the development of IoT solutions. Samsung ARTIK leverages many projects sponsored by the Eclipse Foundation IoT Working Group, including Mosquitto, Paho, KURA, Wakaama and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Samsung ARTIK&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Samsung ARTIK end-to-end, integrated platform unifies hardware, software, cloud, security, and a partner ecosystem in a single offering. ARTIK does the heavy lifting so you can focus on differentiating your products and services. Reduce costs, time and risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Within the platform, the Samsung ARTIK Cloud provides easy-to-use, open, and enterprise-grade APIs, SDKs, and tools in a single integrated platform. Companies can use these APIs, SDKs, and tools to collect, store, and act on any data from any device or cloud service, and speed up their product development process, accelerate time to market and revenue, and improve value to customers.
We specifically focus our activities on the openHAB project, but we are also promoting the ideals of Free software in general.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fortiss GmbH</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/fortiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/fortiss/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;fortiss is an institute associated with the Technical University of Munich and as such a full-fledged academic research institute while enjoying the independence granted by its legal form as a non-profit
organization. Our mandate is to facilitate research and technology transfer in software-intensive systems and services, thereby triggering future ready innovation, with a focus on Bavaria. In this role fortiss
acts as a technological think tank, bridging the notorious gap between fundamental research in academia and its fruitful implementation in an industrially and commercially feasible context. We see this role as a two-way street; preparing advanced fundamental research results for
practical use, but also identifying problems and challenges in industry and communicating them for resolution by academia.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EclipseSource</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/eclipsesource/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/eclipsesource/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EclipseSource is a leader in Eclipse technology and provides you with the expertise to solve your domain challenges. Therefore, we create and adopt innovative as well as proven technology including all essential Eclipse frameworks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EclipseSource is focused on Business Applications, Mobile Applications, Modeling Tools and Frameworks/Developer Tooling. We provide a complete range of services including conception, evaluation, training, support, consulting/implementation with a special focus on framework adoption, creation and maintenance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EclipseSource is distributed over multiple locations in North America and Europe and serves a truly global customer base from various domains, ranging from Fortune 100 corporations to individual developers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Codenvy, S.A.</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/codenvy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 16:47:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/codenvy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Codenvy makes cloud workspaces for development teams. Our product is based on the Eclipse Che project (many of our developers are Che committers) and adds enterprise features and management capabilities to Che. We have worked with Samsung and others to build out IoT-focused development products based on Che.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Codenvy has 50 employees and has raised $9M from Toba Capital, Auriga Ventures, and angels.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IncQuery Labs Ltd.</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/incquery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 15:31:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/incquery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;IncQuery Labs Ltd. is a young and innovative company, founded in 2013 by a group of experts, with over 50 years of total R&amp;amp;D experience in model driven engineering. Our mission is to accelerate technology transfer from top-notch academic research to challenging industrial projects. We offer innovative R&amp;amp;D solutions like:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;high performance modeling tools with innovative traceability support,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;code generators and transformation chains (both batch and incremental),&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tool and runtime development for critical embedded and cyber-physical systems,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;superscalable queries for big data apps, and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;event and stream processing for IoT.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our expertise covers model queries, transformations and compilers, domain-specific language engineering, incremental solutions, performance tuning, configuration design and deployment, tool development and integration in the automotive, avionics, Internet of Things and other domains.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IOTRACKS</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/iotracks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 15:31:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/iotracks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With IOTRACKS fog computing, developing for the edge becomes as easy as developing for the Web.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ioFabric gives you a universal runtime for the edge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ComSat lets you interconnect private locations using the public Internet&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ioAuthoring gives you drag-and-drop microservices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SensorUp</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/sensorup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/sensorup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Data from all your different sensors, accessible in a single platform&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SensorUp makes information from all different kinds of sensors accessible in a single platform, by using open standards to connect the sensors. Our IoT Platform is the world&amp;rsquo;s first, most complete, compliant implementation of the OGC SensorThings API.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SensorThings API was purpose-built for IoT, and manages low power, low bandwidth, and intermittent connectivity situations. The standard isREST-based and JSON encoded,so it&amp;rsquo;s developer friendly. Our easy-to-use APIs and SDKs can be understood and worked with in very little time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siemens</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/siemens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/siemens/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Siemens is a global powerhouse in electrical engineering and electronics. The company has 343,000 employees (as of September 30, 2014) working to develop and manufacture products, design and install complex systems and projects, and tailor a wide range of services for individual requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Electrification, automation and digitalization are the long-term growth fields of Siemens. In order to take full advantage of the market potential in these fields, our businesses are bundled into nine divisions and healthcare as a separately managed business: Power and Gas, Wind Power and Renewables, Power Generation Services, Energy Management, Building Technologies, Mobility, Digital Factory, Process Industries and Drives, Financial Services, and Healthcare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Siemens contributes to various open source projects and also initiated several open source projects.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CA Technologies</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/ca/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CA Technologies (NASDAQ: CA) creates software that fuels transformation for companies and enables them to seize the opportunities of the application economy. Software is at the heart of every business, in every industry. From planning to development to management and security, CA is working with companies worldwide to change the way we live, transact and communicate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CA software and solutions help our customers drive enterprise-wide productivity, offer differentiated user experiences and open new growth opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And, we are able to deliver this value across multiple environments &amp;ndash; mobile, private and public cloud, distributed and mainframe. Our goal is to be recognized by our customers as their critical partner in the new application economy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generative Software</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/generative-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/generative-software/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Generative Software is an Eclipse Solution Member since 2011 and joined the Working Group in summer 2015. It aims to provide DSLs, a canonical IoT meta model and Open-Source code generators that target the Eclipse IoT components and projects. This allows you to design and develop complete IoT solutions in a model-driven way, do rapid prototyping and keep track of the solution’s system and software architecture. At the same time, the Virtual Developer Platform serves as a central place, where many different IoT related generators can be found and all of them are accessed in a uniform way, without installation on a developer’s computer, no matter who develops or owns a generator (device manufacturer, platform vendor, solution developer, …).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huawei</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/huawei/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/huawei/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Huawei Technologies is a high-tech enterprise which specializes in research and development (R&amp;amp;D), production and marketing of communications equipment, providing customized network solutions for telecom carriers in optical, fixed, mobile and data communications networks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Huawei’s IoT platform is open and standard based. It provides a common foundation across different applications and services. Its flexible  and scalable architecture supports both Carrier and Enterprise market. The unified authentication and flexible data management Improves MSISDN Resource Utilization and provides Anti-theft, anti-attack and anti-embezzlement. The IoT SDK connect people and machine seamlessly and enable updatable and secure devices at the edge capable of additional processing and functionality. As a turnkey solution provider huawei IoT solution integrate with difference devices with heterogeneous network access path to allow heterogeneous protocols  to be connected to IoT platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Huawei is the active participant in the open source community.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azul Systems</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/azul/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/azul/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Azul Systems is the world’s only company that is 100% focused on Java and Java runtime technology. We believe that we can help the IoT developers take advantage of the power and productivity of Java by reducing the frictions (licensing costs, field-of-use restrictions) and perceptions (footprint, etc.) gating widespread adoption of the language throughout the IoT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As members of the Eclipse community we are bringing Zulu and Zulu Embedded – our 100% open source JDKs, to the IoT. Our Zulu products are certified builds of OpenJDK and meet the Java SE standards for Java 8, 7 and 6.  Each release of Zulu and Zulu Embedded has passed the thousands of tests in OpenJDK Technology Compatibility Kit (TCK) as well as Azul’s extensive in-house verification suite. Zulu runs on many Linux distros, on Windows and the Mac.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zulu is a complete Java Development Kit, and Zulu Enterprise provides designers with a choice of storage footprint, bitness (32 or 64-bit configurations), headless or headful, and both development and runtime-only options.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Hat, Inc.</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/redhat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/redhat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Red Hat, the world&amp;rsquo;s leading open source solutions provider, is headquartered in Raleigh, NC with over 50 satellite offices spanning the globe. CIOs have ranked Red Hat first for value in Enterprise Software for four consecutive years in the CIO Insight Magazine Vendor Value study.Red Hat provides high-quality, affordable technology with its operating system platform, Red Hat Enterprise Linux, together with applications, management and Services Oriented Architecture (SOA) solutions, including the JBoss Enterprise Middleware Suite. Red Hat also offers support, training and consulting services to its customers worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sierra Wireless</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/sierra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/sierra/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sierra Wireless is the global leader in machine-to-machine (M2M) devices and cloud services, delivering intelligent wireless solutions that simplify the connected world. We offer the industry&amp;rsquo;s most comprehensive portfolio of 2G, 3G and 4G embedded modules and gateways, seamlessly integrated with our secure M2M cloud services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sierra Wireless is deeply involved in the Eclipse IoT community: we founded the IoT Working Group, and are contributing to several projects including Wakaama, Californium, LDT,… The Eclipse IoT technologies are also used in our AirVantage M2M Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>