<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Members on Eclipse IoT</title>
    <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Members on Eclipse IoT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 15:31:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://iot.eclipse.org/member/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cirrus Link</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/cirruslink/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/cirruslink/</guid>
      <description>Cirrus Link Solutions provide secure and reliable IIOT software solutions enabled with MQTT that integrates process information throughout the organization bridging the IT / OT gap while supplying a superior OT solution.
With over 30 years of SCADA and Telemetry experience and the co-inventor of MQTT where M2M and IoT started, Cirrus Links understands the technology requirements to help companies achieve their business objectives. Our experiences and ingenuity has been integral in developing the technology to enable and effectively manage data assets for real-time controls to big data analytics for AI and predictive maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fondazione Bruno Kessler - FBK</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/fbk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/fbk/</guid>
      <description>Fondazione Bruno Kessler - FBK - is a private no profit research institution based in Trento, Italy. FBK is divided in several centres and its mission is to develop both knowledge and expertise in the fields of Information and Communication Technology, Microsystems/Microelectronics and Social science, aiming to conduct technology transfer at the local, national and international industrial level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kynetics</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/kynetics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/kynetics/</guid>
      <description>Kynetics provides full software stacks for the most popular embedded application processors focussing in particular on NXP SoCs. In cooperation with hardware manufacturers, Kynetics has been working on popular embedded products tailoring operating systems Android and Linux based including applications for different industries. Quality of the artifacts is delivered through a continuous integration process from source code management, build and image deployment on target devices. Kynetics leverages a solid background in the development of microservices architectures, and provides to its customers full support to the pipeline of product development in the IoT space, which starts from edge devices and their embedded software stack test and delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nokia</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/nokia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/nokia/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>V2COM</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/v2com/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/v2com/</guid>
      <description>With more than 12 years of Internet of Things (IoT) experience and more than one million devices connected world-wide, V2COM provides a platform to turn products into intelligent connected devices. V2COMs technology accelerates IoT project deployments and their time-to-market. V2COMs core offerings and products serve as an operating system that removes the complexity of data protocols, sensors interfaces, security, microprocessors architecture, software application language and wireless connectivity to create seamless, device intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ADLINK Technology Inc.</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/adlink/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/adlink/</guid>
      <description>ADLINK is ‘Leading EDGE COMPUTING’ by delivering the network nodes that enable practical and scalable IoT systems. Building on its strong heritage in embedded computing, ADLINK provides the hardware and advanced Edge-aware software capabilities necessary for the multi-vendor, multi-standard connectivity required in end-to-end IT/OT business solutions. ADLINK reduces the complexity and helps speed the deployment of enterprise IoT systems that liberate data from vendor silos and other islands-of-automation, thus enabling business improvement in terms of operational excellence, enhanced customer service and support for new business models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orange</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/orange/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/orange/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InfluxData</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/influxdata/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/influxdata/</guid>
      <description>At InfluxData, we see the state of time-based data and have a strong vision about how to move forward — a vision born of our authentic experiences and a conviction that drives us to be the modern engine propelling next-generation systems: a platform that empowers builders to create great things as this data revolution unfolds.
We are singularly focused on reducing the Time to Awesome ™, we truly care about helping developers and businesses get to results faster with less complexity and less code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intel</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/intel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/intel/</guid>
      <description>Intel® Software helps developers to build innovative edge-to-cloud solutions with hardware, software, and data capabilities that make development easy, secure and scalable.
Visit the Intel® Software Developer Zone for IoT to gain access to our complete dev kits, tools, comprehensive code libraries, SDKs, technical content and support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudera</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/cloudera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 15:31:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/cloudera/</guid>
      <description>Cloudera delivers the modern platform for machine learning and advanced analytics built on the latest open source technologies. The world&amp;rsquo;s leading organizations trust Cloudera to help solve their most challenging business problems by efficiently capturing, storing, processing and analyzing vast amounts of data.
Cloudera was founded in 2008 by some of the brightest minds at Silicon Valleys leading companies including Google (Christophe Bisciglia), Yahoo! (Amr Awadallah), Oracle (Mike Olson), and Facebook (Jeff Hammerbacher).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CONTACT Software</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/contact-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/contact-software/</guid>
      <description>CONTACT Software is a leading vendor of software for the product engineering process and the digital transformation.
We connect people, teams and companies. Our mission: Energizing great minds. Instead of rigid systems, we create a working world in which employees can concentrate their skills on providing better products and services. A working world in which collaboration runs more smoothly, processes become more efficient and routine work becomes easier. Our guiding framework provides both security and freedom allowing agile interaction between individuals and teams in complex projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/sap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/sap/</guid>
      <description>As a market leader in enterprise application and digital transformation software, SAP helps companies of all sizes and industries run better. From back office to boardroom, warehouse to storefront, desktop to mobile devices, SAP empowers people and organizations to work together more efficiently by utilizing cloud, analytics, machine learning, Big Data, IoT and other insights more effectively to stay ahead of the competition. SAP applications and open cloud platform services enable more than 296,000 customers in 190 countries to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and grow sustainably.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DB Systel</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/db-systel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/db-systel/</guid>
      <description>DB Systel is using MQTT for a large number of IoT use cases, utilizing Eclipse Paho and Eclipse Mosquitto. We want to actively promote open standards and openness to enable digital innovation in the logistics and transportation industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kichwa Coders</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/kichwa-coders/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/kichwa-coders/</guid>
      <description>At Kichwa Coders we build cutting-edge developer tools for the Internet of Things. We have experience at every level of the IoT stack from cloud to low-level embedded devices. Our clients rate us highly for our focus on excellence in software development, and for our versatility and dynamism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CEA List</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/cealist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/cealist/</guid>
      <description>List, expert on digital systems
Based in Saclay (Paris region, France), List is a public research institute specialized in digital systems design. Its main mission is based on achieving excellence technological development on behalf of industrial partners for value creation.
100 industrial collaborations per year
List institute counts more than 700 partners and every year more than a 100 partnership activities are being conducted with French and foreign industrial companies on applied research projects in four main topics:  Advanced Manufacturing Embedded systems Ambient intelligence Health ionizing radiations  Labeled as Carnot Institute , List invests every year 25% of its budget into scientific resourcing actions in order to identify better tomorrows technological breakthroughs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung ARTIK</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/samsung/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/samsung/</guid>
      <description>Samsung and Eclipse
In an effort to strengthen our commitment to open source development, Samsung Semiconductor Inc. is proud to be a solution member of the Eclipse Foundation. In May 2015, Samsung announced the Samsung ARTIK Smart IoT platform in effort to provide an end-to-end solution to help accelerate the development of IoT solutions. Samsung ARTIK leverages many projects sponsored by the Eclipse Foundation IoT Working Group, including Mosquitto, Paho, KURA, Wakaama and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fortiss GmbH</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/fortiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/fortiss/</guid>
      <description>fortiss is an institute associated with the Technical University of Munich and as such a full-fledged academic research institute while enjoying the independence granted by its legal form as a non-profit organization. Our mandate is to facilitate research and technology transfer in software-intensive systems and services, thereby triggering future ready innovation, with a focus on Bavaria. In this role fortiss acts as a technological think tank, bridging the notorious gap between fundamental research in academia and its fruitful implementation in an industrially and commercially feasible context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EclipseSource</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/eclipsesource/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/eclipsesource/</guid>
      <description>EclipseSource is a leader in Eclipse technology and provides you with the expertise to solve your domain challenges. Therefore, we create and adopt innovative as well as proven technology including all essential Eclipse frameworks.
EclipseSource is focused on Business Applications, Mobile Applications, Modeling Tools and Frameworks/Developer Tooling. We provide a complete range of services including conception, evaluation, training, support, consulting/implementation with a special focus on framework adoption, creation and maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IncQuery Labs Ltd.</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/incquery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 15:31:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/incquery/</guid>
      <description>IncQuery Labs Ltd. is a young and innovative company, founded in 2013 by a group of experts, with over 50 years of total R&amp;amp;D experience in model driven engineering. Our mission is to accelerate technology transfer from top-notch academic research to challenging industrial projects. We offer innovative R&amp;amp;D solutions like:
 high performance modeling tools with innovative traceability support, code generators and transformation chains (both batch and incremental), tool and runtime development for critical embedded and cyber-physical systems, superscalable queries for big data apps, and event and stream processing for IoT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IOTRACKS</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/iotracks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 15:31:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/iotracks/</guid>
      <description>With IOTRACKS fog computing, developing for the edge becomes as easy as developing for the Web.
 ioFabric gives you a universal runtime for the edge ComSat lets you interconnect private locations using the public Internet ioAuthoring gives you drag-and-drop microservices  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SensorUp</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/sensorup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/sensorup/</guid>
      <description>Data from all your different sensors, accessible in a single platform
SensorUp makes information from all different kinds of sensors accessible in a single platform, by using open standards to connect the sensors. Our IoT Platform is the world&amp;rsquo;s first, most complete, compliant implementation of the OGC SensorThings API.
SensorThings API was purpose-built for IoT, and manages low power, low bandwidth, and intermittent connectivity situations. The standard isREST-based and JSON encoded,so it&amp;rsquo;s developer friendly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siemens</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/siemens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/siemens/</guid>
      <description>Siemens is a global powerhouse in electrical engineering and electronics. The company has 343,000 employees (as of September 30, 2014) working to develop and manufacture products, design and install complex systems and projects, and tailor a wide range of services for individual requirements.
Electrification, automation and digitalization are the long-term growth fields of Siemens. In order to take full advantage of the market potential in these fields, our businesses are bundled into nine divisions and healthcare as a separately managed business: Power and Gas, Wind Power and Renewables, Power Generation Services, Energy Management, Building Technologies, Mobility, Digital Factory, Process Industries and Drives, Financial Services, and Healthcare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CA Technologies</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/ca/</guid>
      <description>CA Technologies (NASDAQ: CA) creates software that fuels transformation for companies and enables them to seize the opportunities of the application economy. Software is at the heart of every business, in every industry. From planning to development to management and security, CA is working with companies worldwide to change the way we live, transact and communicate.
CA software and solutions help our customers drive enterprise-wide productivity, offer differentiated user experiences and open new growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generative Software</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/generative-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/generative-software/</guid>
      <description>Generative Software is an Eclipse Solution Member since 2011 and joined the Working Group in summer 2015. It aims to provide DSLs, a canonical IoT meta model and Open-Source code generators that target the Eclipse IoT components and projects. This allows you to design and develop complete IoT solutions in a model-driven way, do rapid prototyping and keep track of the solution’s system and software architecture. At the same time, the Virtual Developer Platform serves as a central place, where many different IoT related generators can be found and all of them are accessed in a uniform way, without installation on a developer’s computer, no matter who develops or owns a generator (device manufacturer, platform vendor, solution developer, …).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huawei</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/huawei/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/huawei/</guid>
      <description>Huawei Technologies is a high-tech enterprise which specializes in research and development (R&amp;amp;D), production and marketing of communications equipment, providing customized network solutions for telecom carriers in optical, fixed, mobile and data communications networks.
Huawei’s IoT platform is open and standard based. It provides a common foundation across different applications and services. Its flexible and scalable architecture supports both Carrier and Enterprise market. The unified authentication and flexible data management Improves MSISDN Resource Utilization and provides Anti-theft, anti-attack and anti-embezzlement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azul Systems</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/azul/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/azul/</guid>
      <description>Azul Systems is the world’s only company that is 100% focused on Java and Java runtime technology. We believe that we can help the IoT developers take advantage of the power and productivity of Java by reducing the frictions (licensing costs, field-of-use restrictions) and perceptions (footprint, etc.) gating widespread adoption of the language throughout the IoT.
As members of the Eclipse community we are bringing Zulu and Zulu Embedded – our 100% open source JDKs, to the IoT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Hat, Inc.</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/redhat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/redhat/</guid>
      <description>Red Hat, the world&amp;rsquo;s leading open source solutions provider, is headquartered in Raleigh, NC with over 50 satellite offices spanning the globe. CIOs have ranked Red Hat first for value in Enterprise Software for four consecutive years in the CIO Insight Magazine Vendor Value study.Red Hat provides high-quality, affordable technology with its operating system platform, Red Hat Enterprise Linux, together with applications, management and Services Oriented Architecture (SOA) solutions, including the JBoss Enterprise Middleware Suite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sierra Wireless</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/sierra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/sierra/</guid>
      <description>Sierra Wireless is the global leader in machine-to-machine (M2M) devices and cloud services, delivering intelligent wireless solutions that simplify the connected world. We offer the industry&amp;rsquo;s most comprehensive portfolio of 2G, 3G and 4G embedded modules and gateways, seamlessly integrated with our secure M2M cloud services.
Sierra Wireless is deeply involved in the Eclipse IoT community: we founded the IoT Working Group, and are contributing to several projects including Wakaama, Californium, LDT,… The Eclipse IoT technologies are also used in our AirVantage M2M Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>openHAB Foundation</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/openhab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/openhab/</guid>
      <description>The openHAB Foundation e.V. is a non-profit organisation.
Its purpose is to educate the public about the possibilities that Free software offers in the domain of smart homes.
More and more new technologies and devices are introduced to our living, working and business environment. Although all of them are designed to make our lives easier, they have a common problem: The lack of interoperability, due to incompatible technology stacks and conflicting commercial interests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Litmus Automation</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/litmus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/litmus/</guid>
      <description>Litmus Automation aims to help businesses adapt to the smart revolution in technology by enabling connected solutions. The company&amp;rsquo;s full-featured Internet of Things platform Loop aids in accelerating revenue generation and operational business impact from connected applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M2M Alliance</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/m2m-alliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/m2m-alliance/</guid>
      <description>As the largest association for the machine-to-machine sector, the M2M Alliance is considered the platform and voice for providers and users of M2M solutions. The primary objective of the M2M Alliance is to promote M2M technologies and solutions. The M2M Alliance actively advocates for the economic interests of its members, and promotes cooperation and the exchange of experiences among the various sectors and companies. The M2M Alliance represents the interests of the M2M industry by creating better general conditions for attractive and lucrative M2M solutions through the constant interaction among industry, R&amp;amp;D and policy makers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LAAS-CNRS</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/laas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/laas/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>itemis</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/itemis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/itemis/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GadgetKeeper</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/gadgetkeeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/gadgetkeeper/</guid>
      <description>GadgetKeeper is an Internet Of Things platform allowing the rapid creation if IoT solutions to connect your sensors, devices, equipment (&amp;ldquo;Things&amp;rdquo;) with people and systems.
GadgetKeeper&amp;rsquo;s technology eliminates complexity by simplifying and standardizing the way information is managed and exchanged so that physical and virtual assets and services can work together as one integrated system.
GadgetKeeper provides you with foundational IoT building blocks (compete object model for things/services, templates and versioning, reach data types, programmable business logic) and services (data storage, time series, multiple communication protocols, integration with external services, life-cycle management and elastic scalability) allowing you to focus on product innovation rather than on enabling infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBH SYSTEMS</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/ibh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/ibh/</guid>
      <description>IBH SYSTEMS GmbH is the lead developer of the Eclipse SCADA system, a true open source SCADA platform.
Eclipse SCADA offers a fully featured SCADA platform from the integration of field devices, over middleware functionality, to HMI components. It provides a communication abstraction layer, monitoring and archival services, a visual interface and a sophisticated system to configure complex SCADA installations. As the lead developer, IBH SYSTEMS GmbH offers consulting, custom development and integration for Eclipse SCADA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/ibm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/ibm/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MicroEJ</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/microej/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/microej/</guid>
      <description>MicroEJ is an independent software vendor of cost-driven solutions for the smart digital world. With more than $20M of R&amp;amp;D investment, MicroEJ is focused on providing turnkey software products to solve the embedded worlds major business challenges and to enable application-driven uses and services in the IoT world commensurate with the cost and resource constraints of that world. MicroEJ helps OEMs create flexible and future-proof smart devices, brings rich user experiences, and enables additional sources of revenue across the whole value chain, from sensor data collection to cloud-based services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deutsche Telekom</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/dtag/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/dtag/</guid>
      <description>QIVICON is an alliance of leading German industrial companies, initiated by Deutsche Telekom AG with the aim of promoting the field of Smart Home technology and providing solutions for customers on a multi-manufacturer basis. Together with its partners EnBW, eQ-3, Miele and Samsung, Deutsche Telekom is developing a platform that covers areas such as energy efficiency, security and convenience in the home for people of every age group. QIVICON enables appliances and functions from different brands to be combined easily in the Smart Home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eurotech</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/eurotech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/eurotech/</guid>
      <description>Eurotech believes in open, standards-based systems to deliver on the promise of the Internet of Things, and works with world-class partners and organizations to evangelize that strategy, including as a founding member of the IoT Working Group in the Eclipse Foundation and OASIS MQTT Technical Committee. Eurotech has contributed the Kura project to the Eclipse Foundation and actively participates in many associated projects and activities.
Eurotech solutions combine software, application framework, hardware, and device cloud services that drive business success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canonical</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/canonical/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/canonical/</guid>
      <description>Canonical is the company behind Ubuntu, the leading Operating System for cloud and Internet of Things. Most public cloud workloads are running on Ubuntu, as do smart gateways, self-driving cars and advanced robots. Canonical has been a proponent of open source since 2004, committed to creating it, refining it, certifying it for reliability and promoting its use.
Canonical leads the development of the snap universal Linux packaging system for secure, transactional device updates and app stores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dc-square</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/dcsquare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/dcsquare/</guid>
      <description>dc-square is a company based in Southern Germany building software solutions for the Internet of Things. Our product HiveMQ is a MQTT broker for the enterprise, which makes it possible to connect thousands and millions of devices over wired or wireless networks with very efficient bandwidth usage and push technology. Our focus is on providing IoT building blocks for the enterprise and advice on, consult on or implement IoT solutions for companies around them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitreactive</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/bitreactive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/bitreactive/</guid>
      <description>Bitreactive makes Reactive Blocks, a tool designed to accelerate and simplify M2M and IoT software development. Its benefits are especially well suited for applications that run autonomously on gateways. Functionality that is often used is provided by dedicated building blocks, for instance for protocols like MQTT or Modbus, access to data collection APIs or processing and buffering of data. The tool checks if applications work correctly with regard to their behavior, and detects a range of errors automatically that are hard to find by traditional testing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bosch Software Innovations</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/bosch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/bosch/</guid>
      <description>Bosch Software Innovations GmbH, the Bosch Group&amp;rsquo;s software and systems house, designs, develops, and operates innovative software and system solutions that help our customers around the world both in the Internet of Things and in the traditional enterprise environment. We place particular focus on the topics of mobility, energy, manufacturing, and smart home.
The focus of the Eclipse Vorto project, which has been proposed by Bosch Software Innovations, is the standardization of so called information models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenText Analytics</title>
      <link>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/opentext/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot.eclipse.org/member/opentext/</guid>
      <description>OpenText Analytics and Reporting products make data-driven applications simple for everyone in your organization, including developers, employees, partners, IT, and customers. Build enterprise reporting applications that are as unique as your business, personalized to meet your data needs in any industry, on any platform, for any device.
To stay competitive, your organization needs to make the right business decisions at the right time, with compelling data to back up your actions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>