<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Members on Eclipse IoT</title>
    <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Members on Eclipse IoT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://iot.eclipse.org/member/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Zolertia</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/zolertia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/zolertia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In Zolertia we provide Internet of Things hardware solutions for industrial partners, universities and R&amp;amp;D.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are helping companies worldwide to connect things to the Internet in order to solve their needs and create faster and more efficient processes and solutions which means less maintenance investment and cost time saving to improve the fully operative structure of the companies that yearly could suppose a waste of millions EUR, with a technology with 30 times more range and 2000 times less power consumption than Wi-Fi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zolertia hardware platforms have been distributed to more than 300 universities, R&amp;amp;D centers, industrial partners and designers like Cisco, Orange, Acciona, Endesa, Sony, Philips, Intel or Siemens in more than 45 different countries.
We hope to help the developing and promotion of IoT open standards, and bring to the developer and maker community the best hardware platforms and tools to achieve this.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azul Systems</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/azul/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/azul/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Azul Systems is the world’s only company that is 100% focused on Java and Java runtime technology. We believe that we can help the IoT developers take advantage of the power and productivity of Java by reducing the frictions (licensing costs, field-of-use restrictions) and perceptions (footprint, etc.) gating widespread adoption of the language throughout the IoT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As members of the Eclipse community we are bringing Zulu and Zulu Embedded – our 100% open source JDKs, to the IoT. Our Zulu products are certified builds of OpenJDK and meet the Java SE standards for Java 8, 7 and 6.  Each release of Zulu and Zulu Embedded has passed the thousands of tests in OpenJDK Technology Compatibility Kit (TCK) as well as Azul’s extensive in-house verification suite. Zulu runs on many Linux distros, on Windows and the Mac.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zulu is a complete Java Development Kit, and Zulu Enterprise provides designers with a choice of storage footprint, bitness (32 or 64-bit configurations), headless or headful, and both development and runtime-only options.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Hat</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/redhat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/redhat/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sierra Wireless</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/sierra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/sierra/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sierra Wireless is the global leader in machine-to-machine (M2M) devices and cloud services, delivering intelligent wireless solutions that simplify the connected world. We offer the industry&amp;rsquo;s most comprehensive portfolio of 2G, 3G and 4G embedded modules and gateways, seamlessly integrated with our secure M2M cloud services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sierra Wireless is deeply involved in the Eclipse IoT community: we founded the IoT Working Group, and are contributing to several projects including Wakaama, Californium, LDT,… The Eclipse IoT technologies are also used in our AirVantage M2M Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>openHAB UG</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/openhab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/openhab/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;openHAB UG (haftungsbeschränkt) is the company behind the open-source home automation solution openHAB and believes that an open-source stack is the only right answer for home gateways. openHAB UG therefore initiated the Eclipse SmartHome project and is the lead developer behind it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Eclipse SmartHome project is a framework that allows building smart home solutions that have a strong focus on heterogeneous environments, i.e. solutions that deal with the integration of different protocols or standards. Its purpose is to provide a uniform access to devices and information and to facilitate different kinds of interactions with them.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Litmus Automation</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/litmus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/litmus/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Litmus Automation aims to help businesses adapt to the smart revolution in technology by enabling connected solutions. The company&amp;rsquo;s full-featured Internet of Things platform Loop aids in accelerating revenue generation and operational business impact from connected applications.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M2M Alliance</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/m2m-alliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/m2m-alliance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As the largest association for the machine-to-machine sector, the M2M Alliance is considered the platform and voice for providers and users of M2M solutions. The primary objective of the M2M Alliance is to promote M2M technologies and solutions. The M2M Alliance actively advocates for the economic interests of its members, and promotes cooperation and the exchange of experiences among the various sectors and companies. The M2M Alliance represents the interests of the M2M industry by creating better general conditions for attractive and lucrative M2M solutions through the constant interaction among industry, R&amp;amp;D and policy makers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LAAS-CNRS</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/laas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/laas/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>itemis</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/itemis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/itemis/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GadgetKeeper</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/gadgetkeeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/gadgetkeeper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GadgetKeeper is an Internet Of Things platform allowing the rapid creation if IoT solutions to connect your sensors, devices, equipment (&amp;ldquo;Things&amp;rdquo;) with people and systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GadgetKeeper&amp;rsquo;s technology eliminates complexity by simplifying and standardizing the way information is managed and exchanged so that physical and virtual assets and services can work together as one integrated system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GadgetKeeper provides you with foundational IoT building blocks (compete object model for things/services, templates and versioning, reach data types, programmable business logic) and services (data storage, time series, multiple communication protocols, integration with external services, life-cycle management and elastic scalability) allowing you to focus on product innovation rather than on enabling infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBH SYSTEMS</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/ibh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/ibh/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;IBH SYSTEMS GmbH is the lead developer of the Eclipse SCADA system, a true open source SCADA platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eclipse SCADA offers a fully featured SCADA platform from the integration of field devices, over middleware functionality, to HMI components. It provides a communication abstraction layer, monitoring and archival services, a visual interface and a sophisticated system to configure complex SCADA installations. As the lead developer, IBH SYSTEMS GmbH offers consulting, custom development and integration for Eclipse SCADA.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/ibm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/ibm/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IS2T</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/is2t/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/is2t/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;IS2T is the editor of the Java-based MicroEJ solution, an open and standard platform dedicated to embedded devices. MicroEJ gives you a powerful SDK and a set of libraries to simulate and develop intelligent applications, and deploy them to MCUs, MPUs, and SOC based devices. MicroEJ adresses the IoT market and focus to intelligent, connected software applications.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMB</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/smb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/smb/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SMB has been an independent IT consulting firm since 1998. We are devoted to providing high-quality RCP and OSGi software development, consulting and training to mid-sized organizations. Additionally we develop independent products and tools based on the Eclipse Rich Client Platform.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deutsche Telekom</title>
      <link>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/dtag/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:31:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iot.eclipse.org/member/dtag/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;QIVICON is an alliance of leading German industrial companies, initiated by Deutsche Telekom AG with the aim of promoting the field of Smart Home technology and providing solutions for customers on a multi-manufacturer basis. Together with its partners EnBW, eQ-3, Miele and Samsung, Deutsche Telekom is developing a platform that covers areas such as energy efficiency, security and convenience in the home for people of every age group. QIVICON enables appliances and functions from different brands to be combined easily in the Smart Home.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>